1	Nordic	nordic	JJ	ORGANIZATION	6	amod
2	International	International	NNP	ORGANIZATION	6	compound
3	Ltd	Ltd	NNP	ORGANIZATION	6	compound
4	v	v	LS	O	6	dep
5	Morten	Morten	NNP	ORGANIZATION	6	compound
6	Innhaug	Innhaug	NNP	ORGANIZATION	0	ROOT
7	-LSB-	-lsb-	-LRB-	O	8	punct
8	2017	2017	CD	DATE	6	nmod
9	-RSB-	-rsb-	-RRB-	O	6	punct
10	SGHC	SGHC	NNP	O	6	dep
11	1	1	CD	NUMBER	10	nummod
12	Case	Case	NNP	O	13	compound
13	Number	Number	NNP	O	10	dep
14	:	:	:	O	6	punct
15	Suit	Suit	NNP	O	16	compound
16	No	No	NNP	O	6	dep
17	875	875	CD	NUMBER	16	nummod
18	of	of	IN	O	19	case
19	2010	2010	CD	DATE	16	nmod
20	Decision	Decision	NNP	O	21	compound
21	Date	Date	NNP	O	16	dep
22	:	:	:	O	6	punct
23	04	04	CD	DATE	26	nummod
24	January	January	NNP	DATE	26	compound
25	2017	2017	CD	DATE	26	nummod
26	Tribunal/Court	Tribunal/Court	NNP	O	6	dep
27	:	:	:	O	26	punct
28	High	High	NNP	ORGANIZATION	30	compound
29	Court	Court	NNP	ORGANIZATION	30	compound
30	Coram	Coram	NNP	ORGANIZATION	26	dep
31	:	:	:	O	6	punct
32	Steven	Steven	NNP	PERSON	35	compound
33	Chong	Chong	NNP	PERSON	35	compound
34	J	J	NNP	PERSON	35	compound
35	Counsel	Counsel	NNP	PERSON	6	dep
36	Name	name	VB	PERSON	35	dep
37	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	38	punct
38	s	s	NNS	O	35	dep
39	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	38	punct
40	:	:	:	O	35	punct
41	Anthony	Anthony	NNP	PERSON	44	compound
42	Soh	Soh	NNP	PERSON	44	compound
43	Leong	Leong	NNP	PERSON	44	compound
44	Kiat	Kiat	NNP	PERSON	35	dep
45	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	48	punct
46	Via	Via	NNP	O	48	compound
47	Law	Law	NNP	O	48	compound
48	Corporation	Corporation	NNP	O	44	appos
49	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	48	punct
50	,	,	,	O	44	punct
51	Andrew	Andrew	NNP	PERSON	54	compound
52	Ho	Ho	NNP	PERSON	54	compound
53	Yew	Yew	NNP	PERSON	54	compound
54	Cheng	Cheng	NNP	PERSON	44	appos
55	and	and	CC	O	54	cc
56	June	June	NNP	DATE	59	compound
57	Lim	Lim	NNP	PERSON	59	compound
58	Pei	Pei	NNP	PERSON	59	compound
59	Ling	Ling	NNP	PERSON	54	conj
60	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	61	punct
61	instructed	instruct	VBN	O	35	dep
62	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	61	punct
63	for	for	IN	O	65	case
64	the	the	DT	O	65	det
65	plaintiff	plaintiff	NN	O	35	nmod
66	;	;	:	O	35	punct
67	Joseph	Joseph	NNP	PERSON	70	compound
68	Tan	Tan	NNP	PERSON	70	compound
69	Wee	Wee	NNP	PERSON	70	compound
70	Kong	Kong	NNP	PERSON	35	dep
71	and	and	CC	O	70	cc
72	Joanna	Joanna	NNP	PERSON	75	compound
73	Poh	Poh	NNP	PERSON	75	compound
74	Ying	Ying	NNP	PERSON	75	compound
75	Ying	Ying	NNP	PERSON	70	conj
76	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	35	punct
77	Legal	Legal	NNP	ORGANIZATION	79	compound
78	Solutions	Solutions	NNPS	ORGANIZATION	79	compound
79	LLC	LLC	NNP	ORGANIZATION	35	dep
80	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	35	punct
81	for	for	IN	O	83	case
82	the	the	DT	O	83	det
83	defendant	defendant	NN	O	35	nmod
84	.	.	.	O	6	punct

1	Parties	party	NNS	O	0	ROOT
2	:	:	:	O	1	punct
3	Companies	company	NNS	O	4	nsubj
4	 	 	VBP	O	1	appos
5	 	 	CD	NUMBER	6	compound
6	 	 	CD	NUMBER	7	nummod
7	Directors	director	NNS	O	8	nsubj
8	 	 	VBP	O	4	ccomp
9	 	 	CD	NUMBER	10	compound
10	 	 	CD	NUMBER	11	nummod
11	Duties	duty	NNS	O	17	nsubj
12	4	4	CD	NUMBER	13	compound
13	 	 	CD	NUMBER	11	nummod
14	January	January	NNP	DATE	11	nmod:tmod
15	 	 	CD	NUMBER	14	nummod
16	2017	2017	CD	DATE	17	nummod
17	Judgment	judgment	NN	O	8	xcomp
18	reserved	reserve	VBN	O	17	acl
19	.	.	.	O	1	punct

1	Steven	Steven	NNP	PERSON	3	compound
2	Chong	Chong	NNP	PERSON	3	compound
3	J	J	NNP	PERSON	0	ROOT
4	:	:	:	O	3	punct
5	Introduction	introduction	NN	O	3	dep
6	1	1	CD	NUMBER	7	compound
7	 	 	CD	NUMBER	8	nummod
8	 	 	NN	O	5	nmod
9	 	 	CD	NUMBER	10	compound
10	 	 	CD	NUMBER	11	nummod
11	 	 	NN	O	8	dep
12	 	 	CD	NUMBER	13	compound
13	 	 	CD	NUMBER	15	nummod
14	The	the	DT	O	15	det
15	parties	party	NNS	O	21	nsubjpass
16	to	to	TO	O	18	case
17	this	this	DT	O	18	det
18	action	action	NN	O	15	nmod
19	have	have	VBP	O	21	aux
20	been	be	VBN	O	21	auxpass
21	embroiled	embroil	VBN	O	11	acl:relcl
22	in	in	IN	O	23	case
23	litigation	litigation	NN	O	21	nmod
24	against	against	IN	O	26	case
25	each	each	DT	O	26	det
26	other	other	JJ	O	21	nmod
27	over	over	IN	O	31	case
28	the	the	DT	DURATION	31	det
29	last	last	JJ	DURATION	31	amod
30	seven	seven	CD	DURATION	31	nummod
31	years	year	NNS	DURATION	26	nmod
32	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	2	det
2	dispute	dispute	NN	O	5	nsubjpass
3	can	can	MD	O	5	aux
4	be	be	VB	O	5	auxpass
5	traced	trace	VBN	O	0	ROOT
6	to	to	TO	O	9	case
7	a	a	DT	O	9	det
8	joint	joint	JJ	O	9	amod
9	venture	venture	NN	O	5	advcl
10	between	between	IN	O	12	case
11	two	two	CD	NUMBER	12	nummod
12	shareholders	shareholder	NNS	O	9	nmod
13	which	which	WDT	O	14	nsubj
14	went	go	VBD	O	12	acl:relcl
15	really	really	RB	O	14	advmod
16	badly	badly	RB	O	14	advmod
17	,	,	,	O	9	punct
18	almost	almost	RB	O	9	dep
19	from	from	IN	O	21	case
20	the	the	DT	O	21	det
21	word	word	NN	O	9	nmod
22	``	``	``	O	21	punct
23	go	go	VB	O	21	dep
24	 	 	NN	O	23	dobj
25	.	.	.	O	5	punct

1	This	this	DT	O	2	det
2	case	case	NN	O	6	nsubj
3	is	be	VBZ	O	6	cop
4	a	a	DT	O	6	det
5	derivative	derivative	JJ	O	6	amod
6	action	action	NN	O	0	ROOT
7	brought	bring	VBN	O	6	acl
8	by	by	IN	O	10	case
9	one	one	CD	NUMBER	10	nummod
10	shareholder	shareholder	NN	O	7	nmod
11	of	of	IN	O	13	case
12	the	the	DT	O	13	det
13	company	company	NN	O	10	nmod
14	against	against	IN	O	16	case
15	a	a	DT	O	16	det
16	director	director	NN	O	7	nmod
17	 	 	VBD	O	16	acl:relcl
18	the	the	DT	O	21	det
19	other	other	JJ	O	21	amod
20	shareholder	shareholder	NN	O	21	compound
21	 	 	NN	O	17	dobj
22	alleging	allege	VBG	O	17	xcomp
23	that	that	IN	O	25	mark
24	he	he	PRP	O	25	nsubj
25	breached	breach	VBD	O	22	ccomp
26	his	he	PRP$	O	28	nmod:poss
27	fiduciary	fiduciary	JJ	O	28	amod
28	duties	duty	NNS	O	25	dobj
29	to	to	TO	O	31	case
30	the	the	DT	O	31	det
31	company	company	NN	O	25	nmod
32	by	by	IN	O	33	mark
33	procuring	procure	VBG	O	25	advcl
34	an	a	DT	O	37	det
35	``	``	``	O	37	punct
36	assignment	assignment	NN	O	37	compound
37	 	 	NN	O	33	dobj
38	of	of	IN	O	40	case
39	a	a	DT	O	40	det
40	charterparty	charterparty	NN	O	37	nmod
41	to	to	TO	O	43	case
42	a	a	DT	O	43	det
43	company	company	NN	O	33	nmod
44	he	he	PRP	O	46	nsubj
45	substantially	substantially	RB	O	46	advmod
46	owned	own	VBD	O	43	acl:relcl
47	,	,	,	O	7	punct
48	on	on	IN	O	49	case
49	terms	term	NNS	O	7	nmod
50	enabling	enable	VBG	O	49	acl
51	him	he	PRP	O	50	dobj
52	to	to	TO	O	53	mark
53	make	make	VB	O	50	xcomp
54	a	a	DT	O	55	det
55	profit	profit	NN	O	53	dobj
56	.	.	.	O	6	punct

1	Besides	besides	IN	O	2	mark
2	seeking	seek	VBG	O	17	advcl
3	to	to	TO	O	4	mark
4	make	make	VB	O	2	xcomp
5	the	the	DT	O	7	det
6	director	director	NN	O	7	compound
7	account	account	NN	O	4	dobj
8	for	for	IN	O	10	case
9	the	the	DT	O	10	det
10	profit	profit	NN	O	4	nmod
11	he	he	PRP	O	13	nsubj
12	has	have	VBZ	O	13	aux
13	made	make	VBN	O	10	acl:relcl
14	,	,	,	O	17	punct
15	the	the	DT	O	16	det
16	company	company	NN	O	17	nsubj
17	seeks	seek	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
18	to	to	TO	O	19	mark
19	hold	hold	VB	O	17	xcomp
20	him	he	PRP	O	21	nsubj
21	liable	liable	JJ	O	19	xcomp
22	for	for	IN	O	24	case
23	the	the	DT	O	24	det
24	loss	loss	NN	O	21	nmod
25	of	of	IN	O	27	case
26	charter	charter	NN	O	27	compound
27	hire	hire	NN	O	24	nmod
28	to	to	TO	O	30	case
29	the	the	DT	O	30	det
30	company	company	NN	O	21	nmod
31	.	.	.	O	17	punct

1	2	2	CD	NUMBER	2	compound
2	 	 	CD	NUMBER	3	nummod
3	 	 	NN	O	16	nsubj
4	 	 	CD	NUMBER	5	compound
5	 	 	CD	NUMBER	6	nummod
6	 	 	NN	O	3	nmod
7	 	 	CD	NUMBER	8	compound
8	 	 	CD	NUMBER	6	dep
9	However	however	RB	O	14	advmod
10	,	,	,	O	14	punct
11	the	the	DT	O	13	det
12	aggrieved	aggrieved	JJ	O	13	amod
13	shareholder	shareholder	NN	O	14	nsubj
14	has	have	VBZ	O	8	acl:relcl
15	itself	itself	PRP	O	14	dobj
16	commenced	commence	VBD	O	0	ROOT
17	another	another	DT	O	19	det
18	derivative	derivative	JJ	O	19	amod
19	action	action	NN	O	16	dobj
20	by	by	IN	O	21	case
21	way	way	NN	O	16	nmod
22	of	of	IN	O	24	case
23	an	a	DT	O	24	det
24	arbitration	arbitration	NN	O	21	nmod
25	on	on	IN	O	26	case
26	behalf	behalf	NN	O	16	nmod
27	of	of	IN	O	29	case
28	the	the	DT	O	29	det
29	company	company	NN	O	26	nmod
30	against	against	IN	O	33	case
31	the	the	DT	O	33	det
32	original	original	JJ	O	33	amod
33	charterer	charterer	NN	O	29	nmod
34	for	for	IN	O	35	case
35	loss	loss	NN	O	33	nmod
36	of	of	IN	O	39	case
37	the	the	DT	O	39	det
38	charter	charter	NN	O	39	compound
39	hire	hire	NN	O	35	nmod
40	.	.	.	O	16	punct

1	If	if	IN	O	6	mark
2	the	the	DT	O	4	det
3	original	original	JJ	O	4	amod
4	charterer	charterer	NN	O	6	nsubjpass
5	is	be	VBZ	O	6	auxpass
6	found	find	VBN	O	17	advcl
7	liable	liable	JJ	O	6	xcomp
8	to	to	TO	O	9	mark
9	pay	pay	VB	O	7	xcomp
10	the	the	DT	O	12	det
11	charter	charter	NN	O	12	compound
12	hire	hire	NN	O	9	dobj
13	,	,	,	O	17	punct
14	then	then	RB	O	15	advmod
15	it	it	PRP	O	17	nsubj
16	may	may	MD	O	17	aux
17	be	be	VB	O	0	ROOT
18	that	that	IN	O	23	mark
19	the	the	DT	O	20	det
20	director	director	NN	O	23	nsubj
21	 	 	CD	NUMBER	22	nummod
22	s	s	NNS	O	20	dep
23	alleged	allege	VBD	O	17	ccomp
24	breach	breach	NN	O	27	nsubj
25	has	have	VBZ	O	27	aux
26	not	not	RB	O	27	neg
27	caused	cause	VBN	O	23	ccomp
28	any	any	DT	O	29	det
29	loss	loss	NN	O	27	dobj
30	of	of	IN	O	32	case
31	charter	charter	NN	O	32	compound
32	hire	hire	NN	O	29	nmod
33	to	to	TO	O	35	case
34	the	the	DT	O	35	det
35	company	company	NN	O	27	nmod
36	.	.	.	O	17	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	3	det
2	present	present	JJ	DATE	3	amod
3	suit	suit	NN	O	5	nsubjpass
4	was	be	VBD	O	5	auxpass
5	bifurcated	bifurcate	VBN	O	0	ROOT
6	and	and	CC	O	5	cc
7	the	the	DT	O	8	det
8	hearing	hearing	NN	O	11	nsubj
9	before	before	IN	O	10	case
10	me	I	PRP	O	8	nmod
11	dealt	deal	VBD	O	5	conj
12	only	only	RB	O	11	advmod
13	with	with	IN	O	15	case
14	the	the	DT	O	15	det
15	question	question	NN	O	11	nmod
16	of	of	IN	O	21	case
17	the	the	DT	O	21	det
18	director	director	NN	O	21	compound
19	 	 	CD	NUMBER	21	nummod
20	s	s	NNS	O	21	compound
21	liability	liability	NN	O	15	nmod
22	for	for	IN	O	23	case
23	breach	breach	NN	O	21	nmod
24	of	of	IN	O	25	case
25	duty	duty	NN	O	23	nmod
26	.	.	.	O	5	punct

1	One	one	CD	NUMBER	8	nsubj
2	of	of	IN	O	4	case
3	the	the	DT	O	4	det
4	issues	issue	NNS	O	1	nmod
5	which	which	WDT	O	7	nsubj
6	hence	hence	RB	O	7	advmod
7	arises	arise	VBZ	O	4	acl:relcl
8	is	be	VBZ	O	25	ccomp
9	whether	whether	IN	O	15	mark
10	,	,	,	O	15	punct
11	assuming	assume	VBG	O	15	csubjpass
12	the	the	DT	O	13	det
13	director	director	NN	O	11	dobj
14	is	be	VBZ	O	15	auxpass
15	found	find	VBN	O	8	ccomp
16	to	to	TO	O	18	mark
17	have	have	VB	O	18	aux
18	breached	breach	VBN	O	15	xcomp
19	his	he	PRP$	O	20	nmod:poss
20	duties	duty	NNS	O	18	dobj
21	,	,	,	O	25	punct
22	the	the	DT	O	23	det
23	court	court	NN	O	25	nsubj
24	should	should	MD	O	25	aux
25	grant	grant	VB	O	0	ROOT
26	a	a	DT	O	27	det
27	declaration	declaration	NN	O	25	dobj
28	to	to	TO	O	30	case
29	that	that	DT	O	30	det
30	effect	effect	NN	O	25	nmod
31	if	if	IN	O	41	mark
32	the	the	DT	O	33	det
33	loss	loss	NN	O	41	nsubj
34	arising	arise	VBG	O	33	acl
35	from	from	IN	O	37	case
36	that	that	DT	O	37	det
37	breach	breach	NN	O	34	nmod
38	might	might	MD	O	41	aux
39	not	not	RB	O	41	neg
40	have	have	VB	O	41	aux
41	crystallised	crystallise	VBN	O	25	advcl
42	as	as	RB	O	43	advmod
43	yet	yet	RB	O	47	advmod
44	given	give	VBN	O	47	case
45	the	the	DT	O	47	det
46	pending	pend	VBG	O	47	amod
47	status	status	NN	O	41	nmod
48	of	of	IN	O	51	case
49	the	the	DT	O	51	det
50	arbitration	arbitration	NN	O	51	compound
51	proceedings	proceedings	NNS	O	47	nmod
52	.	.	.	O	25	punct

1	Would	would	MD	O	15	aux
2	the	the	DT	O	3	det
3	loss	loss	NN	O	15	nsubj
4	of	of	IN	O	7	case
5	the	the	DT	O	7	det
6	charter	charter	NN	O	7	compound
7	hire	hire	NN	O	3	nmod
8	only	only	RB	O	9	advmod
9	crystallise	crystallise	VBP	O	7	acl:relcl
10	if	if	IN	O	13	mark
11	the	the	DT	O	12	det
12	company	company	NN	O	13	nsubj
13	fails	fail	VBZ	O	9	advcl
14	to	to	TO	O	13	nmod
15	recover	recover	VB	O	0	ROOT
16	the	the	DT	O	19	det
17	outstanding	outstanding	JJ	O	19	amod
18	charter	charter	NN	O	19	compound
19	hire	hire	NN	O	15	dobj
20	in	in	IN	O	22	case
21	the	the	DT	O	22	det
22	arbitration	arbitration	NN	O	15	nmod
23	against	against	IN	O	26	case
24	the	the	DT	O	26	det
25	original	original	JJ	O	26	amod
26	charterer	charterer	NN	O	22	nmod
27	,	,	,	O	15	punct
28	or	or	CC	O	15	cc
29	is	be	VBZ	O	15	conj
30	breach	breach	NN	O	29	nsubj
31	of	of	IN	O	32	case
32	director	director	NN	O	30	nmod
33	 	 	CD	NUMBER	34	compound
34	s	s	NNS	O	35	nummod
35	duties	duty	NNS	O	36	nmod:npmod
36	actionable	actionable	JJ	O	32	acl:relcl
37	per	per	FW	O	38	compound
38	se	se	FW	O	36	advmod
39	?	?	.	O	15	punct

1	Background	background	NN	O	6	nsubj
2	The	the	DT	O	4	det
3	joint	joint	JJ	O	4	amod
4	venture	venture	NN	O	1	dep
5	3	3	CD	NUMBER	4	nummod
6	 	 	NN	O	0	ROOT
7	 	 	CD	NUMBER	8	compound
8	 	 	CD	NUMBER	9	nummod
9	 	 	NN	O	6	dobj
10	 	 	CD	NUMBER	9	compound
11	 	 	CD	NUMBER	9	compound
12	 	 	CD	NUMBER	9	compound
13	The	the	DT	O	14	det
14	defendant	defendant	NN	O	9	dep
15	,	,	,	O	9	punct
16	Mr	Mr	NNP	O	18	compound
17	Morten	Morten	NNP	PERSON	18	compound
18	Innhaug	Innhaug	NNP	PERSON	9	appos
19	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	21	punct
20	``	``	``	O	21	punct
21	Morten	Morten	NNP	O	18	dep
22	 	 	NNP	O	21	dep
23	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	21	punct
24	,	,	,	O	18	punct
25	incorporated	incorporate	VBN	O	18	acl
26	the	the	DT	O	27	det
27	plaintiff	plaintiff	NN	O	25	dobj
28	,	,	,	O	27	punct
29	Nordic	nordic	JJ	ORGANIZATION	31	amod
30	International	International	NNP	ORGANIZATION	31	compound
31	Limited	Limited	NNP	ORGANIZATION	27	appos
32	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	31	punct
33	``	``	``	O	36	punct
34	Nordic	nordic	JJ	MISC	36	amod
35	International	international	JJ	MISC	36	amod
36	 	 	NN	MISC	31	dep
37	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	36	punct
38	in	in	IN	O	42	case
39	the	the	DT	O	42	det
40	British	british	JJ	LOCATION	42	amod
41	Virgin	Virgin	NNP	LOCATION	42	compound
42	Islands	Islands	NNPS	LOCATION	36	nmod
43	on	on	IN	O	44	case
44	16	16	CD	DATE	42	nmod
45	January	January	NNP	DATE	42	nmod:tmod
46	2007	2007	CD	DATE	45	nummod
47	-LSB-	-lsb-	-LRB-	O	48	punct
48	note	note	NN	O	36	nmod
49	:	:	:	O	36	punct
50	1	1	CD	NUMBER	36	dep
51	-RSB-	-rsb-	-RRB-	O	27	punct
52	to	to	TO	O	53	mark
53	purchase	purchase	VB	O	25	xcomp
54	a	a	DT	O	56	det
55	fishing	fishing	NN	O	56	compound
56	trawler	trawler	NN	O	53	dobj
57	which	which	WDT	O	60	nsubjpass
58	would	would	MD	O	60	aux
59	be	be	VB	O	60	auxpass
60	converted	convert	VBN	O	56	acl:relcl
61	and	and	CC	O	60	cc
62	equipped	equip	VBN	O	60	conj
63	to	to	TO	O	64	mark
64	operate	operate	VB	O	60	xcomp
65	as	as	IN	O	69	case
66	a	a	DT	O	69	det
67	seismic	seismic	JJ	O	69	amod
68	survey	survey	NN	O	69	compound
69	vessel	vessel	NN	O	64	nmod
70	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	18	punct
71	``	``	``	O	74	punct
72	the	the	DT	O	74	det
73	Vessel	Vessel	NNP	O	74	compound
74	 	 	NN	O	18	dep
75	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	18	punct
76	.	.	.	O	6	punct

1	-LSB-	-lsb-	-LRB-	O	2	nsubj
2	note	note	NN	O	0	ROOT
3	:	:	:	O	2	punct
4	2	2	CD	NUMBER	14	nsubj
5	-RSB-	-rsb-	-RRB-	O	4	punct
6	Morten	Morten	NNP	PERSON	12	nsubj
7	was	be	VBD	O	12	cop
8	then	then	RB	O	12	advmod
9	Nordic	nordic	JJ	O	12	amod
10	International	International	NNP	O	12	compound
11	 	 	CD	NUMBER	12	nummod
12	s	s	NNS	O	4	acl:relcl
13	sole	sole	JJ	O	14	amod
14	shareholder	shareholder	NN	O	2	parataxis
15	and	and	CC	O	14	cc
16	first	first	JJ	ORDINAL	17	amod
17	director	director	NN	O	14	conj
18	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	-LSB-	-lsb-	-LRB-	O	2	punct
2	note	note	NN	O	0	ROOT
3	:	:	:	O	2	punct
4	3	3	CD	NUMBER	7	compound
5	-RSB-	-rsb-	-RRB-	O	7	punct
6	4	4	CD	NUMBER	7	compound
7	 	 	CD	NUMBER	8	nummod
8	 	 	NN	O	2	dep
9	 	 	CD	NUMBER	10	compound
10	 	 	CD	NUMBER	11	nummod
11	 	 	NN	O	8	nmod
12	 	 	CD	NUMBER	13	compound
13	 	 	CD	NUMBER	11	dep
14	Nordic	nordic	JJ	ORGANIZATION	17	amod
15	Maritime	Maritime	NNP	ORGANIZATION	17	compound
16	Pte	Pte	NNP	ORGANIZATION	17	compound
17	Ltd	Ltd	NNP	ORGANIZATION	35	nsubjpass
18	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	17	punct
19	``	``	``	O	22	punct
20	Nordic	nordic	JJ	O	22	amod
21	Maritime	maritime	NN	O	22	compound
22	 	 	NN	O	17	dep
23	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	17	punct
24	,	,	,	O	17	punct
25	of	of	IN	O	26	case
26	which	which	WDT	O	30	nmod
27	Morten	Morten	NNP	PERSON	30	nsubj
28	was	be	VBD	O	30	cop
29	a	a	DT	O	30	det
30	director	director	NN	O	17	acl:relcl
31	and	and	CC	O	30	cc
32	shareholder	shareholder	NN	O	30	conj
33	,	,	,	O	17	punct
34	was	be	VBD	O	35	auxpass
35	appointed	appoint	VBN	O	13	acl:relcl
36	to	to	TO	O	49	mark
37	be	be	VB	O	49	auxpass
38	the	the	DT	O	39	det
39	manager	manager	NN	O	43	nmod:npmod
40	of	of	IN	O	42	case
41	the	the	DT	O	42	det
42	Vessel	Vessel	NNP	O	39	nmod
43	pursuant	pursuant	JJ	O	49	advmod
44	to	to	TO	O	48	case
45	a	a	DT	O	48	det
46	ship	ship	NN	O	48	compound
47	management	management	NN	O	48	compound
48	agreement	agreement	NN	O	43	nmod
49	dated	date	VBN	O	35	xcomp
50	1	1	CD	DATE	49	dobj
51	January	January	NNP	DATE	49	nmod:tmod
52	2007	2007	CD	DATE	51	nummod
53	between	between	IN	O	55	case
54	Nordic	nordic	JJ	ORGANIZATION	55	amod
55	Maritime	Maritime	NNP	ORGANIZATION	13	nmod
56	and	and	CC	O	55	cc
57	Nordic	nordic	JJ	O	58	amod
58	International	International	NNP	O	55	conj
59	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	-LSB-	-lsb-	-LRB-	O	2	punct
2	note	note	NN	O	24	nsubjpass
3	:	:	:	O	2	punct
4	4	4	CD	NUMBER	2	amod
5	-RSB-	-rsb-	-RRB-	O	4	punct
6	5	5	CD	NUMBER	7	compound
7	 	 	CD	NUMBER	8	nummod
8	 	 	NN	O	4	dep
9	 	 	CD	NUMBER	10	compound
10	 	 	CD	NUMBER	8	nummod
11	 	 	NN	O	15	compound
12	 	 	CD	NUMBER	15	nummod
13	 	 	CD	NUMBER	15	nummod
14	Sinwa	Sinwa	NNP	ORGANIZATION	15	compound
15	Limited	Limited	NNP	ORGANIZATION	8	dep
16	,	,	,	O	8	punct
17	a	a	DT	O	18	det
18	company	company	NN	O	8	appos
19	incorporated	incorporate	VBN	O	18	acl
20	in	in	IN	O	21	case
21	Singapore	Singapore	NNP	LOCATION	19	nmod
22	,	,	,	O	2	punct
23	was	be	VBD	O	24	auxpass
24	approached	approach	VBN	O	0	ROOT
25	to	to	TO	O	26	mark
26	invest	invest	VB	O	24	xcomp
27	in	in	IN	O	29	case
28	this	this	DT	O	29	det
29	venture	venture	NN	O	26	nmod
30	.	.	.	O	24	punct

1	This	this	DT	O	2	nsubj
2	led	lead	VBD	O	8	dep
3	to	to	TO	O	6	case
4	a	a	DT	O	6	det
5	shareholder	shareholder	NN	O	6	compound
6	 	 	NN	O	2	nmod
7	s	be	VBZ	O	8	cop
8	agreement	agreement	NN	O	0	ROOT
9	dated	dated	JJ	O	8	amod
10	4	4	CD	DATE	9	nmod:tmod
11	July	July	NNP	DATE	8	nsubj
12	2007	2007	CD	DATE	11	nummod
13	between	between	IN	O	15	case
14	Sinwa	Sinwa	NNP	LOCATION	15	compound
15	Limited	Limited	NNP	LOCATION	11	nmod
16	and	and	CC	O	15	cc
17	Morten	Morten	NNP	PERSON	15	conj
18	,	,	,	O	11	punct
19	pursuant	pursuant	JJ	O	11	amod
20	to	to	TO	O	25	mark
21	which	which	WDT	O	25	dobj
22	each	each	DT	O	23	det
23	party	party	NN	O	25	nsubj
24	would	would	MD	O	25	aux
25	own	own	VB	O	19	advcl
26	50	50	CD	PERCENT	27	nummod
27	percent	percent	NN	PERCENT	25	dobj
28	of	of	IN	O	33	case
29	Nordic	nordic	JJ	O	33	amod
30	International	international	JJ	O	33	amod
31	 	 	NN	O	33	compound
32	s	s	NNS	O	33	compound
33	shares	share	NNS	O	27	nmod
34	.	.	.	O	8	punct

1	-LSB-	-lsb-	-LRB-	O	2	punct
2	note	note	NN	O	0	ROOT
3	:	:	:	O	2	punct
4	5	5	CD	NUMBER	10	nummod
5	-RSB-	-rsb-	-RRB-	O	10	punct
6	Sinwa	Sinwa	NNP	O	10	compound
7	Limited	Limited	NNP	O	10	compound
8	 	 	CD	NUMBER	10	nummod
9	s	s	NNS	O	10	compound
10	rights	rights	NNS	O	13	nsubj
11	were	be	VBD	O	13	cop
12	later	later	RB	O	13	advmod
13	novated	novated	JJ	O	2	dep
14	to	to	TO	O	20	case
15	Sinwa	Sinwa	NNP	ORGANIZATION	20	compound
16	SS	SS	NNP	ORGANIZATION	20	compound
17	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	ORGANIZATION	18	punct
18	HK	HK	NNP	ORGANIZATION	20	appos
19	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	ORGANIZATION	18	punct
20	Co	Co	NNP	ORGANIZATION	13	nmod
21	Ltd	Ltd	NNP	ORGANIZATION	20	amod
22	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	24	punct
23	``	``	``	O	24	punct
24	Sinwa	sinwa	FW	O	21	dep
25	 	 	FW	O	24	dep
26	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	24	punct
27	,	,	,	O	20	punct
28	a	a	DT	O	29	det
29	company	company	NN	O	30	dobj
30	incorporated	incorporate	VBN	O	20	acl
31	in	in	IN	O	33	case
32	Hong	Hong	NNP	LOCATION	33	compound
33	Kong	Kong	NNP	LOCATION	30	nmod
34	,	,	,	O	13	punct
35	by	by	IN	O	38	case
36	a	a	DT	O	38	det
37	novation	novation	NN	O	38	compound
38	agreement	agreement	NN	O	13	nmod
39	dated	date	VBN	O	38	acl
40	28	28	CD	DATE	39	dobj
41	August	August	NNP	DATE	39	nmod:tmod
42	2007	2007	CD	DATE	41	nummod
43	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	-LSB-	-lsb-	-LRB-	O	2	punct
2	note	note	NN	O	0	ROOT
3	:	:	:	O	2	punct
4	6	6	CD	NUMBER	7	compound
5	-RSB-	-rsb-	-RRB-	O	7	punct
6	6	6	CD	NUMBER	7	compound
7	 	 	CD	NUMBER	8	nummod
8	 	 	NN	O	2	dep
9	 	 	CD	NUMBER	10	compound
10	 	 	CD	NUMBER	11	nummod
11	 	 	NN	O	8	nmod
12	 	 	CD	NUMBER	13	compound
13	 	 	CD	NUMBER	11	dep
14	Sinwa	Sinwa	NNP	O	15	nsubj
15	exercised	exercise	VBD	O	13	acl:relcl
16	its	its	PRP$	O	17	nmod:poss
17	right	right	NN	O	23	nsubj
18	under	under	IN	O	21	case
19	the	the	DT	O	21	det
20	shareholder	shareholder	NN	O	21	compound
21	 	 	NN	O	17	nmod
22	s	be	VBZ	O	23	cop
23	agreement	agreement	NN	O	15	ccomp
24	to	to	TO	O	25	mark
25	nominate	nominate	VB	O	23	acl
26	Mr	Mr	NNP	O	29	compound
27	Sim	Sim	NNP	PERSON	29	compound
28	Yong	Yong	NNP	PERSON	29	compound
29	Teng	Teng	NNP	PERSON	25	dobj
30	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	32	punct
31	``	``	``	O	32	punct
32	Mike	Mike	NNP	O	29	dep
33	Sim	Sim	NNP	O	32	dep
34	 	 	NN	O	33	dep
35	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	32	punct
36	and	and	CC	O	29	cc
37	Ms	Ms	NNP	O	40	compound
38	Tan	Tan	NNP	PERSON	40	compound
39	Lay	Lay	NNP	PERSON	40	compound
40	Ling	Ling	NNP	PERSON	29	conj
41	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	43	punct
42	``	``	``	O	43	punct
43	Lay	Lay	NNP	O	40	dep
44	Ling	Ling	NNP	O	43	dep
45	 	 	NN	O	44	dep
46	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	43	punct
47	as	as	IN	O	48	case
48	directors	director	NNS	O	25	nmod
49	of	of	IN	O	51	case
50	Nordic	nordic	JJ	O	51	amod
51	International	International	NNP	O	48	nmod
52	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	57	punct
53	``	``	``	O	56	punct
54	the	the	DT	O	56	det
55	Sinwa	Sinwa	NNP	MISC	56	compound
56	directors	director	NNS	O	57	nsubj
57	 	 	VBP	O	48	dep
58	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	57	punct
59	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	-LSB-	-lsb-	-LRB-	O	2	punct
2	note	note	NN	O	0	ROOT
3	:	:	:	O	2	punct
4	7	7	CD	NUMBER	2	dep
5	-RSB-	-rsb-	-RRB-	O	4	punct
6	Morten	Morten	NNP	PERSON	7	nsubj
7	nominated	nominate	VBD	O	4	acl:relcl
8	himself	himself	PRP	O	7	dobj
9	and	and	CC	O	8	cc
10	Mr	Mr	NNP	O	12	compound
11	Kjell	Kjell	NNP	PERSON	12	compound
12	Gaukshiem	Gaukshiem	NNP	PERSON	8	conj
13	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	15	punct
14	``	``	``	O	15	punct
15	Kjell	Kjell	NNP	O	8	dep
16	 	 	NNP	O	15	dep
17	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	15	punct
18	as	as	IN	O	19	case
19	directors	director	NNS	O	7	nmod
20	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	2	det
2	four	four	CD	NUMBER	5	nsubj
3	of	of	IN	O	4	case
4	them	they	PRP	O	2	nmod
5	made	make	VBD	O	0	ROOT
6	up	up	RP	O	5	compound:prt
7	the	the	DT	O	8	det
8	board	board	NN	O	5	dobj
9	of	of	IN	O	11	case
10	Nordic	nordic	JJ	ORGANIZATION	11	amod
11	International	International	NNP	ORGANIZATION	8	nmod
12	at	at	IN	O	15	case
13	all	all	DT	O	15	det
14	material	material	JJ	O	15	amod
15	times	time	NNS	O	5	nmod
16	.	.	.	O	5	punct

1	7	7	CD	NUMBER	3	nummod
2	 	 	CD	NUMBER	3	nummod
3	 	 	NN	O	11	nsubjpass
4	 	 	CD	NUMBER	6	nummod
5	 	 	CD	NUMBER	6	nummod
6	 	 	NN	O	3	dep
7	 	 	CD	NUMBER	8	compound
8	 	 	CD	NUMBER	3	dep
9	Sinwa	Sinwa	NNP	O	8	appos
10	was	be	VBD	O	11	auxpass
11	brought	bring	VBN	O	0	ROOT
12	in	in	IN	O	11	nmod
13	to	to	TO	O	14	mark
14	finance	finance	VB	O	11	xcomp
15	the	the	DT	O	17	det
16	joint	joint	JJ	O	17	amod
17	venture	venture	NN	O	14	dobj
18	,	,	,	O	14	punct
19	in	in	IN	O	20	case
20	particular	particular	JJ	O	14	advcl
21	,	,	,	O	14	punct
22	to	to	TO	O	23	mark
23	procure	procure	VB	O	14	advcl
24	financing	financing	NN	O	23	dobj
25	from	from	IN	O	27	case
26	the	the	DT	O	27	det
27	banks	bank	NNS	O	23	nmod
28	for	for	IN	O	30	case
29	the	the	DT	O	30	det
30	retrofitting	retrofitting	NN	O	27	nmod
31	of	of	IN	O	33	case
32	the	the	DT	O	33	det
33	Vessel	Vessel	NNP	O	30	nmod
34	.	.	.	O	11	punct

1	-LSB-	-lsb-	-LRB-	O	2	punct
2	note	note	NN	O	0	ROOT
3	:	:	:	O	2	punct
4	8	8	CD	NUMBER	6	nummod
5	-RSB-	-rsb-	-RRB-	O	6	punct
6	Pursuant	Pursuant	NNP	O	12	nsubj
7	to	to	TO	O	10	case
8	the	the	DT	O	10	det
9	shareholder	shareholder	NN	O	10	compound
10	 	 	NN	O	6	nmod
11	s	be	VBZ	O	12	cop
12	agreement	agreement	NN	O	2	parataxis
13	,	,	,	O	15	punct
14	Sinwa	Sinwa	NNP	PERSON	15	nsubj
15	injected	inject	VBD	O	12	dep
16	US$	us$	$	MONEY	17	dep
17	2m	2m	CD	MONEY	15	dobj
18	working	work	VBG	O	17	acl
19	capital	capital	NN	O	18	dobj
20	into	into	IN	O	22	case
21	Nordic	nordic	JJ	O	22	amod
22	International	International	NNP	O	18	nmod
23	,	,	,	O	15	punct
24	of	of	IN	O	25	case
25	which	which	WDT	O	29	nmod
26	US$	us$	$	MONEY	27	dep
27	25,000	25,000	CD	MONEY	29	nsubjpass
28	was	be	VBD	O	29	auxpass
29	used	use	VBN	O	12	acl:relcl
30	to	to	TO	O	31	mark
31	purchase	purchase	VB	O	29	xcomp
32	its	its	PRP$	O	35	nmod:poss
33	50	50	CD	PERCENT	35	nummod
34	percent	percent	NN	PERCENT	35	compound
35	shareholding	shareholding	NN	O	31	dobj
36	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	-LSB-	-lsb-	-LRB-	O	2	punct
2	note	note	NN	O	0	ROOT
3	:	:	:	O	2	punct
4	9	9	CD	NUMBER	7	advmod
5	-RSB-	-rsb-	-RRB-	O	4	punct
6	In	in	IN	O	7	case
7	September	September	NNP	DATE	11	nmod
8	2007	2007	CD	DATE	7	nummod
9	,	,	,	O	11	punct
10	it	it	PRP	O	11	nsubj
11	guaranteed	guarantee	VBD	O	2	parataxis
12	a	a	DT	O	14	det
13	term	term	NN	O	14	compound
14	loan	loan	NN	O	11	dobj
15	of	of	IN	O	17	case
16	US$	us$	$	MONEY	17	dep
17	16m	16m	CD	MONEY	14	nmod
18	that	that	WDT	O	28	dobj
19	Oversea-Chinese	Oversea-Chinese	NNP	ORGANIZATION	21	compound
20	Banking	Banking	NNP	ORGANIZATION	21	compound
21	Corporation	Corporation	NNP	ORGANIZATION	28	nsubj
22	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	24	punct
23	``	``	``	O	24	punct
24	OCBC	OCBC	NNP	ORGANIZATION	21	dep
25	 	 	CD	NUMBER	24	dep
26	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	24	punct
27	had	have	VBD	O	28	aux
28	extended	extend	VBN	O	17	acl:relcl
29	to	to	TO	O	31	case
30	Nordic	nordic	JJ	O	31	amod
31	International	International	NNP	O	28	nmod
32	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	-LSB-	-lsb-	-LRB-	O	2	punct
2	note	note	NN	O	0	ROOT
3	:	:	:	O	2	punct
4	10	10	CD	NUMBER	2	dep
5	-RSB-	-rsb-	-RRB-	O	4	punct
6	The	the	DT	O	7	det
7	loan	loan	NN	O	9	nsubjpass
8	was	be	VBD	O	9	auxpass
9	used	use	VBN	O	4	acl:relcl
10	to	to	TO	O	11	mark
11	finance	finance	VB	O	9	xcomp
12	the	the	DT	O	13	det
13	conversion	conversion	NN	O	11	dobj
14	of	of	IN	O	16	case
15	the	the	DT	O	16	det
16	Vessel	Vessel	NNP	O	13	nmod
17	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	-LSB-	-lsb-	-LRB-	O	2	punct
2	note	note	NN	O	0	ROOT
3	:	:	:	O	2	punct
4	11	11	CD	NUMBER	2	dep
5	-RSB-	-rsb-	-RRB-	O	8	punct
6	8	8	CD	NUMBER	7	compound
7	 	 	CD	NUMBER	8	nummod
8	 	 	NN	O	4	nmod
9	 	 	CD	NUMBER	11	nummod
10	 	 	CD	NUMBER	11	nummod
11	 	 	NN	O	22	nsubj
12	 	 	CD	NUMBER	13	compound
13	 	 	CD	NUMBER	11	nummod
14	At	at	IN	O	16	case
15	the	the	DT	O	16	det
16	time	time	NN	DATE	11	nmod
17	of	of	IN	O	20	case
18	the	the	DT	O	20	det
19	shareholder	shareholder	NN	O	20	compound
20	 	 	NN	O	16	nmod
21	s	be	VBZ	O	22	cop
22	agreement	agreement	NN	O	4	acl:relcl
23	,	,	,	O	22	punct
24	Morten	Morten	NNP	PERSON	27	nsubj
25	had	have	VBD	O	27	aux
26	already	already	RB	O	27	advmod
27	secured	secure	VBN	O	22	acl:relcl
28	a	a	DT	O	29	det
29	charterparty	charterparty	NN	O	27	dobj
30	dated	date	VBN	O	29	acl
31	8	8	CD	DATE	30	dobj
32	June	June	NNP	DATE	30	nmod:tmod
33	2007	2007	CD	DATE	32	nummod
34	-LSB-	-lsb-	-LRB-	O	35	punct
35	note	note	NN	O	30	nmod
36	:	:	:	O	2	punct
37	12	12	CD	NUMBER	2	dep
38	-RSB-	-rsb-	-RRB-	O	37	punct
39	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	42	punct
40	``	``	``	O	42	punct
41	the	the	DT	O	42	det
42	Time	Time	NNP	MISC	37	dep
43	Charter	Charter	NNP	MISC	42	dep
44	 	 	NN	MISC	43	dep
45	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	42	punct
46	to	to	TO	O	47	case
47	charter	charter	NN	O	37	nmod
48	the	the	DT	O	49	det
49	Vessel	vessel	NN	O	37	dep
50	to	to	TO	O	52	case
51	a	a	DT	O	52	det
52	company	company	NN	O	49	nmod
53	,	,	,	O	2	punct
54	BGP	bgp	NN	ORGANIZATION	57	compound
55	Geoexplorer	Geoexplorer	NNP	ORGANIZATION	57	compound
56	Pte	Pte	NNP	ORGANIZATION	57	compound
57	Ltd	Ltd	NNP	ORGANIZATION	2	appos
58	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	60	punct
59	``	``	``	O	60	punct
60	BGP	bgp	NN	O	57	appos
61	 	 	NN	O	60	dep
62	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	60	punct
63	for	for	IN	O	66	case
64	a	a	DT	O	66	det
65	minimum	minimum	JJ	O	66	amod
66	period	period	NN	O	57	nmod
67	of	of	IN	O	69	case
68	three	three	CD	DURATION	69	nummod
69	years	year	NNS	DURATION	66	nmod
70	at	at	IN	O	74	case
71	a	a	DT	O	74	det
72	very	very	RB	O	73	advmod
73	lucrative	lucrative	JJ	O	74	amod
74	rate	rate	NN	O	69	nmod
75	of	of	IN	O	77	case
76	US$	us$	$	MONEY	77	dep
77	37,000	37,000	CD	MONEY	74	nmod
78	per	per	IN	O	79	case
79	day	day	NN	DURATION	77	nmod
80	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	82	punct
81	which	which	WDT	O	82	nsubj
82	worked	work	VBD	O	74	dep
83	out	out	RP	O	82	compound:prt
84	to	to	TO	O	88	mark
85	be	be	VB	O	88	cop
86	about	about	IN	O	88	case
87	US$	us$	$	MONEY	88	dep
88	1m	1m	CD	MONEY	82	xcomp
89	per	per	IN	O	90	case
90	month	month	NN	DURATION	88	nmod
91	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	82	punct
92	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	BGP	bgp	NN	O	5	nsubj
2	had	have	VBD	O	1	acl
3	in	in	IN	O	4	case
4	turn	turn	NN	O	2	nmod
5	contracted	contract	VBD	O	20	dep
6	,	,	,	O	5	punct
7	in	in	IN	O	8	case
8	December	December	NNP	DATE	5	nmod
9	2006	2006	CD	DATE	8	nummod
10	,	,	,	O	5	punct
11	to	to	TO	O	12	mark
12	provide	provide	VB	O	5	xcomp
13	seismic	seismic	JJ	O	15	amod
14	survey	survey	NN	O	15	compound
15	services	service	NNS	O	12	dobj
16	to	to	TO	O	19	case
17	a	a	DT	O	19	det
18	US	US	NNP	ORGANIZATION	19	compound
19	company	company	NN	ORGANIZATION	12	nmod
20	named	name	VBD	ORGANIZATION	0	ROOT
21	TGS-NOPEC	TGS-NOPEC	NNP	ORGANIZATION	24	compound
22	Geophysical	Geophysical	NNP	ORGANIZATION	24	compound
23	Company	Company	NNP	ORGANIZATION	24	compound
24	SA	SA	NNP	ORGANIZATION	20	nsubj
25	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	27	punct
26	``	``	``	O	27	punct
27	TGS	tgs	NN	O	24	appos
28	 	 	NN	O	27	dep
29	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	27	punct
30	.	.	.	O	20	punct

1	-LSB-	-lsb-	-LRB-	O	2	punct
2	note	note	NN	O	0	ROOT
3	:	:	:	O	2	punct
4	13	13	CD	NUMBER	6	nummod
5	-RSB-	-rsb-	-RRB-	O	6	punct
6	BGP	bgp	NN	O	2	dep
7	intended	intend	VBN	O	6	acl
8	to	to	TO	O	9	mark
9	use	use	VB	O	7	xcomp
10	the	the	DT	O	11	det
11	Vessel	vessel	NN	O	9	dobj
12	to	to	TO	O	13	mark
13	fulfil	fulfil	VB	O	11	acl
14	its	its	PRP$	O	15	nmod:poss
15	obligation	obligation	NN	O	13	dobj
16	in	in	IN	O	18	case
17	the	the	DT	O	18	det
18	provision	provision	NN	O	13	nmod
19	of	of	IN	O	22	case
20	seismic	seismic	JJ	O	22	amod
21	survey	survey	NN	O	22	compound
22	services	service	NNS	O	18	nmod
23	to	to	TO	O	24	case
24	TGS	tgs	NN	ORGANIZATION	9	nmod
25	under	under	IN	O	29	case
26	the	the	DT	O	29	det
27	seismic	seismic	JJ	O	29	amod
28	services	service	NNS	O	29	compound
29	agreement	agreement	NN	O	9	nmod
30	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	9	9	CD	NUMBER	2	nummod
2	 	 	NN	O	51	nsubjpass
3	 	 	CD	NUMBER	4	compound
4	 	 	CD	NUMBER	5	nummod
5	 	 	NN	O	2	nmod
6	 	 	CD	NUMBER	5	compound
7	 	 	CD	NUMBER	5	compound
8	 	 	CD	NUMBER	5	compound
9	From	from	IN	O	5	case
10	Sinwa	sinwa	JJ	O	13	amod
11	 	 	NN	O	13	compound
12	s	s	NNS	O	13	compound
13	perspective	perspective	NN	O	5	dep
14	,	,	,	O	51	punct
15	given	give	VBN	O	23	mark
16	that	that	IN	O	23	mark
17	the	the	DT	O	19	det
18	Time	Time	NNP	MISC	19	compound
19	Charter	Charter	NNP	MISC	23	nsubjpass
20	had	have	VBD	O	23	aux
21	already	already	RB	O	23	advmod
22	been	be	VBN	O	23	auxpass
23	signed	sign	VBN	O	51	advcl
24	prior	prior	RB	O	27	advmod
25	to	to	TO	O	27	case
26	its	its	PRP$	O	27	nmod:poss
27	participation	participation	NN	O	23	advcl
28	and	and	CC	O	23	cc
29	hence	hence	RB	O	43	advmod
30	,	,	,	O	43	punct
31	the	the	DT	O	32	det
32	source	source	NN	O	43	nsubjpass
33	of	of	IN	O	37	case
34	a	a	DT	O	37	det
35	very	very	RB	O	36	advmod
36	attractive	attractive	JJ	O	37	amod
37	stream	stream	NN	O	32	nmod
38	of	of	IN	O	39	case
39	income	income	NN	O	37	nmod
40	had	have	VBD	O	43	aux
41	already	already	RB	O	43	advmod
42	been	be	VBN	O	43	auxpass
43	secured	secure	VBN	O	23	conj
44	,	,	,	O	51	punct
45	its	its	PRP$	O	46	nmod:poss
46	investment	investment	NN	O	51	nsubjpass
47	in	in	IN	O	49	case
48	Nordic	nordic	JJ	MISC	49	amod
49	International	International	NNP	MISC	46	nmod
50	was	be	VBD	O	51	auxpass
51	viewed	view	VBN	O	0	ROOT
52	as	as	IN	O	56	case
53	a	a	DT	O	56	det
54	sound	sound	JJ	O	56	amod
55	business	business	NN	O	56	compound
56	deal	deal	NN	O	51	nmod
57	-LSB-	-lsb-	-LRB-	O	58	punct
58	note	note	NN	O	56	nmod
59	:	:	:	O	56	punct
60	14	14	CD	NUMBER	56	dep
61	-RSB-	-rsb-	-RRB-	O	60	punct
62	and	and	CC	O	60	cc
63	a	a	DT	O	64	det
64	no-brainer	no-brainer	NN	O	60	conj
65	 	 	CD	NUMBER	64	nummod
66	so	so	IN	O	68	mark
67	it	it	PRP	O	68	nsubj
68	thought	think	VBD	O	51	advcl
69	.	.	.	O	51	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	3	det
2	purported	purported	JJ	O	3	amod
3	assignment	assignment	NN	O	17	dep
4	of	of	IN	O	7	case
5	the	the	DT	O	7	det
6	Time	Time	NNP	MISC	7	compound
7	Charter	Charter	NNP	MISC	3	nmod
8	and	and	CC	O	3	cc
9	seismic	seismic	JJ	O	11	amod
10	services	service	NNS	O	11	compound
11	agreement	agreement	NN	O	3	conj
12	10	10	CD	NUMBER	13	compound
13	 	 	CD	NUMBER	11	dep
14	 	 	NN	O	17	dep
15	 	 	CD	NUMBER	14	nummod
16	 	 	CD	NUMBER	17	compound
17	 	 	CD	NUMBER	46	dep
18	Shortly	shortly	RB	O	21	advmod
19	after	after	IN	O	21	case
20	the	the	DT	O	21	det
21	commencement	commencement	NN	O	17	nmod
22	of	of	IN	O	25	case
23	the	the	DT	O	25	det
24	Time	Time	NNP	O	25	compound
25	Charter	Charter	NNP	O	21	nmod
26	,	,	,	O	17	punct
27	due	due	JJ	O	17	amod
28	to	to	TO	O	29	case
29	problems	problem	NNS	O	27	nmod
30	in	in	IN	O	32	case
31	the	the	DT	O	32	det
32	operation	operation	NN	O	29	nmod
33	of	of	IN	O	35	case
34	the	the	DT	O	35	det
35	Vessel	vessel	NN	O	32	nmod
36	and	and	CC	O	17	cc
37	a	a	DT	O	38	det
38	downturn	downturn	NN	O	17	conj
39	in	in	IN	O	41	case
40	the	the	DT	O	41	det
41	market	market	NN	O	38	nmod
42	,	,	,	O	41	punct
43	-LSB-	-lsb-	-LRB-	O	44	punct
44	note	note	NN	O	41	appos
45	:	:	:	O	46	punct
46	15	15	CD	NUMBER	0	ROOT
47	-RSB-	-rsb-	-RRB-	O	46	punct
48	BGP	BGP	NNP	O	49	nsubj
49	indicated	indicate	VBD	O	46	acl:relcl
50	its	its	PRP$	O	51	nmod:poss
51	wish	wish	NN	O	49	dobj
52	to	to	TO	O	53	case
53	Morten	Morten	NNP	PERSON	49	nmod
54	,	,	,	O	49	punct
55	in	in	IN	O	56	case
56	August	August	NNP	DATE	49	nmod
57	2008	2008	CD	DATE	56	nummod
58	,	,	,	O	49	punct
59	to	to	TO	O	61	mark
60	``	``	``	O	61	punct
61	cancel	cancel	VB	O	49	advcl
62	 	 	CD	NUMBER	61	advmod
63	the	the	DT	O	65	det
64	Time	Time	NNP	O	65	compound
65	Charter	Charter	NNP	O	61	dobj
66	.	.	.	O	46	punct

1	Morten	Morten	NNP	PERSON	2	nsubj
2	understood	understand	VBD	O	0	ROOT
3	BGP	bgp	NN	O	2	dobj
4	to	to	TO	O	5	mark
5	mean	mean	VB	O	2	advcl
6	that	that	IN	O	8	mark
7	it	it	PRP	O	8	nsubj
8	wanted	want	VBD	O	5	ccomp
9	to	to	TO	O	11	mark
10	``	``	``	O	11	punct
11	get	get	VB	O	8	xcomp
12	out	out	RP	O	11	compound:prt
13	 	 	NN	O	11	dobj
14	of	of	IN	O	15	mark
15	having	have	VBG	O	13	acl
16	to	to	TO	O	17	mark
17	perform	perform	VB	O	15	xcomp
18	the	the	DT	O	20	det
19	Time	Time	NNP	O	20	compound
20	Charter	Charter	NNP	O	17	dobj
21	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	-LSB-	-lsb-	-LRB-	O	2	punct
2	note	note	NN	O	0	ROOT
3	:	:	:	O	2	punct
4	16	16	CD	NUMBER	2	dep
5	-RSB-	-rsb-	-RRB-	O	8	punct
6	11	11	CD	NUMBER	7	compound
7	 	 	CD	NUMBER	8	nummod
8	 	 	NN	O	4	nmod
9	 	 	CD	NUMBER	8	compound
10	 	 	CD	NUMBER	8	compound
11	 	 	CD	NUMBER	8	compound
12	Morten	Morten	NNP	PERSON	14	nsubj
13	then	then	RB	O	14	advmod
14	entered	enter	VBD	O	4	acl:relcl
15	into	into	IN	O	16	case
16	discussions	discussion	NNS	O	14	nmod
17	with	with	IN	O	18	case
18	BGP	bgp	NN	O	16	nmod
19	and	and	CC	O	18	cc
20	TGS	tgs	NN	ORGANIZATION	18	conj
21	with	with	IN	O	23	case
22	a	a	DT	O	23	det
23	view	view	NN	O	14	nmod
24	to	to	TO	O	26	mark
25	``	``	``	O	26	punct
26	assign	assign	VB	O	14	xcomp
27	 	 	CD	NUMBER	28	nummod
28	BGP	bgp	NN	O	26	dobj
29	 	 	CD	NUMBER	31	nummod
30	s	s	NNS	O	31	compound
31	rights	rights	NNS	O	28	dep
32	and	and	CC	O	28	cc
33	obligations	obligation	NNS	O	28	conj
34	under	under	IN	O	37	case
35	the	the	DT	O	37	det
36	Time	Time	NNP	MISC	37	compound
37	Charter	Charter	NNP	MISC	33	nmod
38	and	and	CC	O	37	cc
39	the	the	DT	O	42	det
40	seismic	seismic	JJ	O	42	amod
41	services	service	NNS	O	42	compound
42	agreement	agreement	NN	O	37	conj
43	to	to	TO	O	45	case
44	Nordic	nordic	JJ	ORGANIZATION	45	amod
45	Maritime	Maritime	NNP	ORGANIZATION	26	nmod
46	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	This	this	DT	O	3	nsubjpass
2	was	be	VBD	O	3	auxpass
3	done	do	VBN	O	0	ROOT
4	without	without	IN	O	7	case
5	the	the	DT	O	7	det
6	prior	prior	JJ	O	7	amod
7	knowledge	knowledge	NN	O	3	nmod
8	or	or	CC	O	7	cc
9	consent	consent	NN	O	7	conj
10	of	of	IN	O	12	case
11	the	the	DT	O	12	det
12	board	board	NN	O	7	nmod
13	of	of	IN	O	14	case
14	directors	director	NNS	O	12	nmod
15	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	-LSB-	-lsb-	-LRB-	O	2	punct
2	note	note	NN	O	0	ROOT
3	:	:	:	O	2	punct
4	17	17	CD	NUMBER	2	dep
5	-RSB-	-rsb-	-RRB-	O	8	punct
6	12	12	CD	NUMBER	7	compound
7	 	 	CD	NUMBER	8	nummod
8	 	 	NN	O	4	nmod
9	 	 	CD	NUMBER	8	compound
10	 	 	CD	NUMBER	8	compound
11	 	 	CD	NUMBER	8	compound
12	In	in	IN	O	14	case
13	an	a	DT	O	14	det
14	email	email	NN	O	31	nmod
15	from	from	IN	O	16	case
16	Morten	Morten	NNP	PERSON	14	nmod
17	to	to	TO	O	18	case
18	BGP	BGP	NNP	O	16	nmod
19	dated	date	VBN	O	18	acl
20	19	19	CD	DATE	19	dobj
21	August	August	NNP	DATE	19	nmod:tmod
22	2008	2008	CD	DATE	21	nummod
23	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	24	punct
24	copied	copy	VBN	O	16	dep
25	only	only	RB	O	24	advmod
26	to	to	TO	O	27	case
27	Kjell	Kjell	NNP	PERSON	24	nmod
28	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	24	punct
29	,	,	,	O	31	punct
30	Morten	Morten	NNP	PERSON	31	nsubj
31	noted	note	VBD	O	4	acl:relcl
32	that	that	IN	O	36	mark
33	BGP	bgp	NN	O	36	nsubj
34	had	have	VBD	O	36	aux
35	already	already	RB	O	36	advmod
36	invested	invest	VBN	O	31	ccomp
37	about	about	IN	O	43	case
38	US$	us$	$	MONEY	41	dep
39	2m	2m	CD	MONEY	41	compound
40	to	to	TO	O	41	dep
41	US$	us$	$	MONEY	43	nummod
42	2.5	2.5	CD	MONEY	41	nummod
43	m	m	NN	O	36	nmod
44	in	in	IN	O	46	case
45	the	the	DT	O	46	det
46	project	project	NN	O	43	nmod
47	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	-LSB-	-lsb-	-LRB-	O	2	punct
2	note	note	NN	O	0	ROOT
3	:	:	:	O	2	punct
4	18	18	CD	NUMBER	2	dep
5	-RSB-	-rsb-	-RRB-	O	4	punct
6	He	he	PRP	O	7	nsubj
7	continued	continue	VBD	O	4	acl:relcl
8	:	:	:	O	7	punct
9	We	we	PRP	O	10	nsubj
10	think	think	VBP	O	7	parataxis
11	that	that	IN	O	68	mark
12	if	if	IN	O	15	mark
13	we	we	PRP	O	15	nsubj
14	could	could	MD	O	15	aux
15	agree	agree	VB	O	68	advcl
16	a	a	DT	O	17	det
17	compensation	compensation	NN	O	15	dobj
18	to	to	TO	O	19	case
19	BGP	bgp	NN	O	15	nmod
20	in	in	IN	O	22	case
21	the	the	DT	O	22	det
22	amount	amount	NN	O	19	nmod
23	that	that	IN	O	26	mark
24	we	we	PRP	O	26	nsubj
25	have	have	VBP	O	26	aux
26	discussed	discuss	VBN	O	15	ccomp
27	above	above	IN	O	30	mark
28	we	we	PRP	O	30	nsubj
29	could	could	MD	O	30	aux
30	get	get	VB	O	26	advcl
31	acceptance	acceptance	NN	O	30	dobj
32	from	from	IN	O	34	case
33	the	the	DT	O	34	det
34	board	board	NN	O	30	nmod
35	of	of	IN	O	38	case
36	Nordic	nordic	JJ	ORGANIZATION	38	amod
37	International	International	NNP	ORGANIZATION	38	compound
38	Limited	Limited	NNP	ORGANIZATION	34	nmod
39	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	40	punct
40	Owners	Owners	NNP	O	38	dep
41	of	of	IN	O	43	case
42	BGP	BGP	NNP	O	43	compound
43	Atlas	Atlas	NNP	O	40	nmod
44	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	40	punct
45	to	to	TO	O	46	mark
46	cancel	cancel	VB	O	30	advcl
47	the	the	DT	O	49	det
48	TC	TC	NNP	MISC	49	compound
49	Contract	Contract	NNP	MISC	46	dobj
50	and	and	CC	O	26	cc
51	that	that	IN	O	54	mark
52	we	we	PRP	O	54	nsubj
53	subsequently	subsequently	RB	O	54	advmod
54	transfer	transfer	VB	O	26	conj
55	the	the	DT	O	56	det
56	operation	operation	NN	O	54	dobj
57	of	of	IN	O	59	case
58	the	the	DT	O	59	det
59	vessel	vessel	NN	O	56	nmod
60	to	to	TO	O	64	case
61	Nordic	nordic	JJ	ORGANIZATION	64	amod
62	Maritime	Maritime	NNP	ORGANIZATION	64	compound
63	Pte	Pte	NNP	ORGANIZATION	64	compound
64	Ltd.	Ltd.	NNP	ORGANIZATION	59	nmod
65	It	it	PRP	O	68	nsubjpass
66	is	be	VBZ	O	68	auxpass
67	also	also	RB	O	68	advmod
68	understood	understand	VBN	O	10	ccomp
69	that	that	IN	O	78	mark
70	a	a	DT	O	71	det
71	part	part	NN	O	78	nsubj
72	of	of	IN	O	75	case
73	the	the	DT	O	75	det
74	cancelation	cancelation	NN	O	75	compound
75	agreement	agreement	NN	O	71	nmod
76	will	will	MD	O	78	aux
77	be	be	VB	O	78	cop
78	that	that	IN	O	68	ccomp
79	:	:	:	O	7	punct
80	1	1	LS	NUMBER	83	dep
81	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	80	punct
82	BGP	bgp	NN	O	83	nsubj
83	assign	assign	VBP	O	7	parataxis
84	the	the	DT	O	86	det
85	Seismic	seismic	JJ	MISC	86	amod
86	contract	contract	NN	O	83	dobj
87	with	with	IN	O	89	case
88	-LSB-	-lsb-	-LRB-	O	89	punct
89	TGS	tgs	NN	ORGANIZATION	86	nmod
90	-RSB-	-rsb-	-RRB-	O	83	punct
91	to	to	TO	O	95	case
92	Nordic	nordic	JJ	MISC	95	amod
93	 	 	NN	O	95	compound
94	-LSB-	-lsb-	-LRB-	O	95	punct
95	emphasis	emphasis	NN	O	83	nmod
96	added	add	VBN	O	95	acl
97	-RSB-	-rsb-	-RRB-	O	100	punct
98	13	13	CD	NUMBER	99	compound
99	 	 	CD	NUMBER	100	nummod
100	 	 	NN	O	96	nmod
101	 	 	CD	NUMBER	100	compound
102	 	 	CD	NUMBER	100	compound
103	 	 	CD	NUMBER	100	compound
104	Morten	Morten	NNP	PERSON	4	dep
105	clarified	clarify	VBN	O	104	acl
106	during	during	IN	O	108	case
107	the	the	DT	O	108	det
108	trial	trial	NN	O	105	nmod
109	that	that	WDT	O	113	nsubj
110	by	by	IN	O	112	case
111	``	``	``	O	112	punct
112	we	we	PRP	O	113	nmod
113	 	 	VBP	O	108	acl:relcl
114	he	he	PRP	O	116	nsubj
115	was	be	VBD	O	116	aux
116	referring	refer	VBG	O	113	ccomp
117	to	to	TO	O	120	case
118	both	both	DT	O	120	det
119	Nordic	nordic	JJ	O	120	amod
120	International	International	NNP	O	116	nmod
121	and	and	CC	O	120	cc
122	Nordic	nordic	JJ	O	123	amod
123	Maritime	Maritime	NNP	O	120	conj
124	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	-LSB-	-lsb-	-LRB-	O	15	punct
2	note	note	NN	O	15	nsubj
3	:	:	:	O	15	punct
4	19	19	CD	NUMBER	14	dep
5	-RSB-	-rsb-	-RRB-	O	4	punct
6	Since	since	IN	O	14	mark
7	he	he	PRP	O	14	nsubj
8	was	be	VBD	O	14	cop
9	``	``	``	O	14	punct
10	in	in	IN	O	14	case
11	all	all	PDT	O	14	det:predet
12	the	the	DT	O	14	det
13	Nordic	nordic	JJ	MISC	14	amod
14	companies	company	NNS	O	15	parataxis
15	 	 	VBP	O	18	advcl
16	,	,	,	O	18	punct
17	he	he	PRP	O	18	nsubj
18	was	be	VBD	O	0	ROOT
19	purportedly	purportedly	RB	O	18	advmod
20	``	``	``	O	21	punct
21	talking	talk	VBG	O	18	ccomp
22	on	on	IN	O	23	case
23	behalf	behalf	NN	O	21	nmod
24	of	of	IN	O	26	case
25	the	the	DT	O	26	det
26	group	group	NN	O	23	nmod
27	 	 	CD	NUMBER	26	nummod
28	.	.	.	O	18	punct

1	-LSB-	-lsb-	-LRB-	O	2	nsubj
2	note	note	NN	O	0	ROOT
3	:	:	:	O	2	punct
4	20	20	CD	NUMBER	2	dobj
5	-RSB-	-rsb-	-RRB-	O	4	punct
6	It	it	PRP	O	12	nsubj
7	was	be	VBD	O	12	cop
8	,	,	,	O	12	punct
9	however	however	RB	O	12	advmod
10	,	,	,	O	12	punct
11	strictly	strictly	RB	O	12	advmod
12	incorrect	incorrect	JJ	O	4	acl:relcl
13	of	of	IN	O	14	case
14	Morten	Morten	NNP	PERSON	4	nmod
15	to	to	TO	O	16	mark
16	refer	refer	VB	O	2	parataxis
17	to	to	TO	O	20	case
18	the	the	DT	O	20	det
19	``	``	``	O	20	punct
20	group	group	NN	O	16	nmod
21	''	''	''	O	20	punct
22	since	since	IN	O	24	mark
23	Sinwa	Sinwa	NNP	ORGANIZATION	24	nsubj
24	has	have	VBZ	O	16	advcl
25	no	no	DT	O	26	neg
26	interest	interest	NN	O	24	dobj
27	in	in	IN	O	30	case
28	the	the	DT	O	30	det
29	Nordic	nordic	JJ	MISC	30	amod
30	companies	company	NNS	O	26	nmod
31	apart	apart	RB	O	30	advmod
32	from	from	IN	O	34	case
33	Nordic	nordic	JJ	ORGANIZATION	34	amod
34	International	International	NNP	ORGANIZATION	31	nmod
35	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	14	14	CD	NUMBER	8	nsubj
2	 	 	CD	NUMBER	3	nummod
3	 	 	NN	O	1	dep
4	 	 	CD	NUMBER	5	compound
5	 	 	CD	NUMBER	1	dep
6	 	 	NN	O	7	compound
7	BGP	bgp	NN	O	5	dep
8	indicated	indicate	VBD	O	0	ROOT
9	its	its	PRP$	O	11	nmod:poss
10	in-principle	in-principle	JJ	O	11	amod
11	agreement	agreement	NN	O	8	dobj
12	to	to	TO	O	14	case
13	this	this	DT	O	14	det
14	proposal	proposal	NN	O	8	nmod
15	on	on	IN	O	16	case
16	20	20	CD	DATE	8	nmod
17	August	August	NNP	DATE	8	nmod:tmod
18	2008	2008	CD	DATE	17	nummod
19	.	.	.	O	8	punct

1	-LSB-	-lsb-	-LRB-	O	2	punct
2	note	note	NN	O	0	ROOT
3	:	:	:	O	2	punct
4	21	21	CD	NUMBER	7	nummod
5	-RSB-	-rsb-	-RRB-	O	7	punct
6	15	15	CD	NUMBER	7	compound
7	 	 	CD	NUMBER	2	dep
8	 	 	NN	O	12	nummod
9	 	 	CD	NUMBER	8	compound
10	 	 	CD	NUMBER	8	compound
11	 	 	CD	NUMBER	8	compound
12	BGP	bgp	NN	O	13	nmod:npmod
13	thereafter	thereafter	RB	O	14	advmod
14	negotiated	negotiate	VBN	O	7	dep
15	with	with	IN	O	16	case
16	TGS	tgs	NN	ORGANIZATION	14	nmod
17	and	and	CC	O	14	cc
18	obtained	obtain	VBD	O	14	conj
19	its	its	PRP$	O	20	nmod:poss
20	agreement	agreement	NN	O	18	dobj
21	to	to	TO	O	22	mark
22	assign	assign	VB	O	18	advcl
23	the	the	DT	O	26	det
24	seismic	seismic	JJ	O	26	amod
25	services	service	NNS	O	26	compound
26	agreement	agreement	NN	O	22	dobj
27	either	either	CC	O	30	cc:preconj
28	to	to	TO	O	30	case
29	Nordic	nordic	JJ	ORGANIZATION	30	amod
30	Maritime	maritime	NN	ORGANIZATION	22	nmod
31	or	or	CC	O	30	cc
32	to	to	TO	O	34	case
33	a	a	DT	O	34	det
34	company	company	NN	O	30	conj
35	to	to	TO	O	37	mark
36	be	be	VB	O	37	auxpass
37	incorporated	incorporate	VBN	O	22	advcl
38	by	by	IN	O	39	case
39	Morten	Morten	NNP	PERSON	37	nmod
40	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	-LSB-	-lsb-	-LRB-	O	2	punct
2	note	note	NN	O	0	ROOT
3	:	:	:	O	2	punct
4	22	22	CD	NUMBER	2	dep
5	-RSB-	-rsb-	-RRB-	O	8	punct
6	16	16	CD	NUMBER	7	compound
7	 	 	CD	NUMBER	8	nummod
8	 	 	NN	O	4	nmod
9	 	 	CD	NUMBER	8	compound
10	 	 	CD	NUMBER	8	compound
11	 	 	CD	NUMBER	8	compound
12	BGP	bgp	NN	O	16	nsubj
13	and	and	CC	O	12	cc
14	TGS	tgs	NN	ORGANIZATION	12	conj
15	then	then	RB	O	16	advmod
16	prepared	prepare	VBD	O	4	acl:relcl
17	a	a	DT	O	19	det
18	tripartite	tripartite	JJ	O	19	amod
19	Memorandum	memorandum	NN	O	16	dobj
20	of	of	IN	O	21	case
21	Agreement	agreement	NN	O	19	nmod
22	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	24	punct
23	``	``	``	O	24	punct
24	MOA	moa	NN	O	16	dep
25	 	 	NN	O	24	dep
26	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	24	punct
27	-LSB-	-lsb-	-LRB-	O	28	punct
28	note	note	NN	O	16	nmod
29	:	:	:	O	2	punct
30	23	23	CD	NUMBER	2	dep
31	-RSB-	-rsb-	-RRB-	O	30	punct
32	which	which	WDT	O	35	nsubjpass
33	was	be	VBD	O	35	auxpass
34	eventually	eventually	RB	O	35	advmod
35	signed	sign	VBN	O	30	acl:relcl
36	on	on	IN	O	37	case
37	23	23	CD	DATE	35	nmod
38	August	August	NNP	DATE	35	nmod:tmod
39	2008	2008	CD	DATE	38	nummod
40	by	by	IN	O	41	case
41	BGP	bgp	NN	O	35	nmod
42	,	,	,	O	41	punct
43	Nordic	nordic	JJ	O	44	amod
44	Maritime	Maritime	NNP	O	41	conj
45	and	and	CC	O	41	cc
46	TGS	TGS	NNP	ORGANIZATION	41	conj
47	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	-LSB-	-lsb-	-LRB-	O	2	punct
2	note	note	NN	O	0	ROOT
3	:	:	:	O	2	punct
4	24	24	CD	NUMBER	2	dep
5	-RSB-	-rsb-	-RRB-	O	4	punct
6	It	it	PRP	O	9	nsubj
7	is	be	VBZ	O	9	cop
8	not	not	RB	O	9	neg
9	insignificant	insignificant	JJ	O	4	acl:relcl
10	that	that	IN	O	21	mark
11	in	in	IN	O	15	case
12	the	the	DT	O	15	det
13	original	original	JJ	O	15	amod
14	draft	draft	NN	O	15	compound
15	MOA	moa	NN	O	21	nmod
16	,	,	,	O	21	punct
17	Nordic	nordic	JJ	MISC	18	amod
18	International	International	NNP	MISC	21	nsubjpass
19	was	be	VBD	O	21	auxpass
20	also	also	RB	O	21	advmod
21	supposed	suppose	VBN	O	9	ccomp
22	to	to	TO	O	25	mark
23	be	be	VB	O	25	cop
24	a	a	DT	O	25	det
25	party	party	NN	O	21	xcomp
26	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	-LSB-	-lsb-	-LRB-	O	2	punct
2	note	note	NN	O	0	ROOT
3	:	:	:	O	2	punct
4	25	25	CD	NUMBER	2	dep
5	-RSB-	-rsb-	-RRB-	O	4	punct
6	It	it	PRP	O	9	nsubj
7	was	be	VBD	O	9	cop
8	obviously	obviously	RB	O	9	advmod
9	sensible	sensible	JJ	O	4	acl:relcl
10	to	to	TO	O	11	mark
11	include	include	VB	O	9	xcomp
12	Nordic	nordic	JJ	ORGANIZATION	13	amod
13	International	International	NNP	ORGANIZATION	11	dobj
14	,	,	,	O	13	punct
15	the	the	DT	O	17	det
16	very	very	RB	O	17	advmod
17	party	party	NN	O	13	appos
18	who	who	WP	O	20	nsubj
19	had	have	VBD	O	20	aux
20	chartered	charter	VBN	O	17	acl:relcl
21	the	the	DT	O	22	det
22	Vessel	vessel	NN	O	20	dobj
23	to	to	TO	O	24	case
24	BGP	bgp	NN	O	20	nmod
25	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	Morten	Morten	NNP	PERSON	4	nsubj
2	was	be	VBD	O	4	cop
3	not	not	RB	O	4	neg
4	able	able	JJ	O	0	ROOT
5	to	to	TO	O	6	mark
6	explain	explain	VB	O	4	xcomp
7	why	why	WRB	O	12	advmod
8	Nordic	nordic	JJ	ORGANIZATION	9	amod
9	International	International	NNP	ORGANIZATION	12	nsubjpass
10	was	be	VBD	O	12	auxpass
11	eventually	eventually	RB	O	12	advmod
12	excluded	exclude	VBN	O	6	advcl
13	as	as	IN	O	15	case
14	a	a	DT	O	15	det
15	party	party	NN	O	12	nmod
16	but	but	CC	O	4	cc
17	it	it	PRP	O	18	nsubj
18	appears	appear	VBZ	O	4	conj
19	that	that	IN	O	29	mark
20	its	its	PRP$	O	22	nmod:poss
21	eventual	eventual	JJ	O	22	amod
22	exclusion	exclusion	NN	O	29	nsubj
23	from	from	IN	O	25	case
24	the	the	DT	O	25	det
25	MOA	MOA	NNP	ORGANIZATION	22	nmod
26	was	be	VBD	O	29	cop
27	probably	probably	RB	O	29	advmod
28	a	a	DT	O	29	det
29	recognition	recognition	NN	O	18	ccomp
30	by	by	IN	O	31	case
31	Morten	Morten	NNP	PERSON	29	nmod
32	,	,	,	O	31	punct
33	BGP	BGP	NNP	ORGANIZATION	31	conj
34	and	and	CC	O	31	cc
35	TGS	TGS	NNP	ORGANIZATION	31	conj
36	that	that	WDT	O	41	dobj
37	Nordic	nordic	JJ	O	38	amod
38	International	international	NN	O	41	nsubj
39	might	might	MD	O	41	aux
40	either	either	RB	O	41	advmod
41	disagree	disagree	VB	O	29	dep
42	or	or	CC	O	41	cc
43	raise	raise	VB	O	41	conj
44	objections	objection	NNS	O	41	dobj
45	to	to	TO	O	46	case
46	it	it	PRP	O	41	nmod
47	.	.	.	O	4	punct

1	This	this	DT	O	3	nsubjpass
2	is	be	VBZ	O	3	auxpass
3	explained	explain	VBN	O	0	ROOT
4	at	at	IN	O	6	case
5	-LSB-	-lsb-	-LRB-	O	6	punct
6	66	66	CD	NUMBER	3	nmod
7	-RSB-	-rsb-	-RRB-	O	6	punct
8	below	below	IN	O	6	advmod
9	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	17	17	CD	NUMBER	2	nummod
2	 	 	CD	NUMBER	13	nsubj
3	 	 	NN	O	2	dep
4	 	 	CD	NUMBER	3	nummod
5	 	 	CD	NUMBER	6	compound
6	 	 	CD	NUMBER	9	nummod
7	The	the	DT	O	9	det
8	material	material	NN	O	9	compound
9	terms	term	NNS	O	2	dep
10	of	of	IN	O	12	case
11	the	the	DT	O	12	det
12	MOA	MOA	NNP	O	9	nmod
13	were	be	VBD	O	0	ROOT
14	as	as	IN	O	15	mark
15	follows	follow	VBZ	O	13	advcl
16	:	:	:	O	15	punct
17	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	18	punct
18	a	a	LS	O	21	dep
19	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	18	punct
20	 	 	CD	NUMBER	21	nummod
21	 	 	CD	NUMBER	15	dobj
22	 	 	NN	O	21	nmod
23	 	 	CD	NUMBER	24	compound
24	 	 	CD	NUMBER	22	nummod
25	BGP	bgp	NN	O	22	dep
26	would	would	MD	O	28	aux
27	``	``	``	O	28	punct
28	transfer	transfer	VB	O	25	acl:relcl
29	and	and	CC	O	28	cc
30	assign	assign	VB	O	28	conj
31	all	all	DT	O	32	det
32	rights	rights	NNS	O	28	dobj
33	and	and	CC	O	32	cc
34	obligations	obligation	NNS	O	32	conj
35	 	 	CD	NUMBER	34	nummod
36	under	under	IN	O	39	case
37	the	the	DT	O	39	det
38	Time	Time	NNP	MISC	39	compound
39	Charter	Charter	NNP	MISC	28	nmod
40	and	and	CC	O	21	cc
41	the	the	DT	O	44	det
42	seismic	seismic	JJ	O	44	amod
43	services	service	NNS	O	44	compound
44	agreement	agreement	NN	O	21	conj
45	to	to	TO	O	47	case
46	Nordic	nordic	JJ	ORGANIZATION	47	amod
47	Maritime	Maritime	NNP	ORGANIZATION	44	nmod
48	.	.	.	O	13	punct

1	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	2	punct
2	b	b	NN	O	13	dep
3	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	2	punct
4	 	 	CD	NUMBER	5	nummod
5	 	 	CD	NUMBER	13	nsubj
6	 	 	NN	O	13	nmod
7	 	 	CD	NUMBER	8	compound
8	 	 	CD	NUMBER	6	dep
9	BGP	bgp	NN	O	8	dep
10	would	would	MD	O	13	aux
11	be	be	VB	O	13	cop
12	``	``	``	O	13	punct
13	relieved	relieved	JJ	O	0	ROOT
14	and	and	CC	O	13	cc
15	released	release	VBN	O	13	conj
16	of	of	IN	O	18	case
17	the	the	DT	O	18	det
18	obligations	obligation	NNS	O	15	nmod
19	under	under	IN	O	23	case
20	the	the	DT	O	23	det
21	Time	Time	NNP	MISC	23	compound
22	Charter	Charter	NNP	MISC	23	compound
23	 	 	NN	O	15	nmod
24	and	and	CC	O	23	cc
25	the	the	DT	O	28	det
26	seismic	seismic	JJ	O	28	amod
27	services	service	NNS	O	28	compound
28	agreement	agreement	NN	O	23	conj
29	.	.	.	O	13	punct

1	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	2	punct
2	c	c	NN	O	5	dep
3	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	2	punct
4	 	 	CD	NUMBER	5	nummod
5	 	 	CD	NUMBER	0	ROOT
6	 	 	NN	O	5	nmod
7	 	 	CD	NUMBER	8	compound
8	 	 	CD	NUMBER	6	nummod
9	The	the	DT	O	10	det
10	parties	party	NNS	O	6	dep
11	to	to	TO	O	15	case
12	the	the	DT	O	15	det
13	seismic	seismic	JJ	O	15	amod
14	services	service	NNS	O	15	compound
15	agreement	agreement	NN	O	10	nmod
16	would	would	MD	O	19	aux
17	be	be	VB	O	19	cop
18	Nordic	nordic	JJ	ORGANIZATION	19	amod
19	Maritime	Maritime	NNP	ORGANIZATION	15	acl:relcl
20	and	and	CC	O	19	cc
21	TGS	TGS	NNP	ORGANIZATION	19	conj
22	.	.	.	O	5	punct

1	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	2	punct
2	d	d	NN	O	27	nsubj
3	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	2	punct
4	 	 	CD	NUMBER	6	nummod
5	 	 	CD	NUMBER	6	nummod
6	 	 	NN	O	2	dep
7	 	 	CD	NUMBER	8	compound
8	 	 	CD	NUMBER	11	nummod
9	The	the	DT	O	11	det
10	daily	daily	JJ	SET	11	amod
11	rate	rate	NN	O	2	dep
12	payable	payable	JJ	O	11	amod
13	by	by	IN	O	14	case
14	TGS	tgs	NN	ORGANIZATION	12	nmod
15	to	to	TO	O	17	case
16	Nordic	nordic	JJ	O	17	amod
17	Maritime	Maritime	NNP	O	12	nmod
18	for	for	IN	O	20	case
19	the	the	DT	O	20	det
20	provision	provision	NN	O	11	nmod
21	of	of	IN	O	23	case
22	seismic	seismic	JJ	O	23	amod
23	services	service	NNS	O	20	nmod
24	would	would	MD	O	27	aux
25	be	be	VB	O	27	cop
26	US$	us$	$	MONEY	27	dep
27	52,500	52,500	CD	MONEY	0	ROOT
28	.	.	.	O	27	punct

1	This	this	DT	O	10	nsubjpass
2	was	be	VBD	O	10	auxpass
3	US$	us$	$	MONEY	4	dep
4	5,000	5,000	CD	MONEY	5	nmod:npmod
5	more	more	JJR	O	10	advmod
6	than	than	IN	O	9	case
7	the	the	DT	O	9	det
8	daily	daily	JJ	SET	9	amod
9	rate	rate	NN	O	5	nmod
10	paid	pay	VBN	O	52	ccomp
11	by	by	IN	O	12	case
12	TGS	tgs	NN	ORGANIZATION	10	nmod
13	to	to	TO	O	14	case
14	BGP	bgp	NN	O	10	nmod
15	,	,	,	O	14	punct
16	which	which	WDT	O	21	nsubj
17	was	be	VBD	O	21	cop
18	US$	us$	$	MONEY	21	nummod
19	47,500	47,500	CD	MONEY	18	compound
20	-LSB-	-lsb-	-LRB-	O	18	punct
21	note	note	NN	O	14	acl:relcl
22	:	:	:	O	21	punct
23	26	26	CD	NUMBER	21	dep
24	-RSB-	-rsb-	-RRB-	O	27	punct
25	18	18	CD	NUMBER	26	compound
26	 	 	CD	NUMBER	27	nummod
27	 	 	NN	O	23	nmod
28	 	 	CD	NUMBER	27	compound
29	 	 	CD	NUMBER	27	compound
30	 	 	CD	NUMBER	27	compound
31	Given	give	VBN	O	23	acl
32	that	that	IN	O	40	mark
33	the	the	DT	O	35	det
34	charter	charter	NN	O	35	compound
35	hire	hire	NN	O	40	nsubj
36	payable	payable	JJ	O	35	amod
37	to	to	TO	O	39	case
38	Nordic	nordic	JJ	O	39	amod
39	International	International	NNP	O	36	nmod
40	remained	remain	VBD	O	31	ccomp
41	fixed	fix	VBN	O	40	xcomp
42	at	at	IN	O	44	case
43	US$	us$	$	MONEY	44	dep
44	37,000	37,000	CD	MONEY	41	nmod
45	,	,	,	O	10	punct
46	following	follow	VBG	O	48	case
47	the	the	DT	O	48	det
48	assignment	assignment	NN	O	10	nmod
49	,	,	,	O	52	punct
50	Nordic	nordic	JJ	O	51	amod
51	Maritime	Maritime	NNP	O	52	nsubj
52	stood	stand	VBD	O	0	ROOT
53	to	to	TO	O	54	mark
54	make	make	VB	O	52	xcomp
55	US$	us$	$	MONEY	56	dep
56	15,500	15,500	CD	MONEY	54	dobj
57	a	a	DT	DURATION	58	det
58	day	day	NN	DURATION	56	dep
59	,	,	,	O	56	punct
60	which	which	WDT	O	63	nsubj
61	was	be	VBD	O	63	cop
62	US$	us$	$	MONEY	63	dep
63	5,000	5,000	CD	MONEY	56	acl:relcl
64	per	per	IN	O	65	case
65	day	day	NN	DURATION	63	nmod
66	more	more	RBR	O	63	advmod
67	than	than	IN	O	69	mark
68	BGP	bgp	NN	O	69	nsubj
69	did	do	VBD	O	66	advcl
70	,	,	,	O	66	punct
71	from	from	IN	O	73	case
72	the	the	DT	O	73	det
73	assignments	assignment	NNS	O	66	nmod
74	of	of	IN	O	78	case
75	both	both	CC	O	78	cc:preconj
76	the	the	DT	O	78	det
77	Time	Time	NNP	MISC	78	compound
78	Charter	Charter	NNP	MISC	73	nmod
79	and	and	CC	O	78	cc
80	the	the	DT	O	83	det
81	seismic	seismic	JJ	O	83	amod
82	services	service	NNS	O	83	compound
83	agreement	agreement	NN	O	78	conj
84	.	.	.	O	52	punct

1	19	19	CD	NUMBER	2	nummod
2	 	 	CD	NUMBER	3	nsubj
3	 	 	NN	O	0	ROOT
4	 	 	CD	NUMBER	3	dobj
5	 	 	CD	NUMBER	6	compound
6	 	 	CD	NUMBER	9	nummod
7	The	the	DT	O	9	det
8	purported	purported	JJ	O	9	amod
9	assignment	assignment	NN	O	15	nsubjpass
10	of	of	IN	O	13	case
11	the	the	DT	O	13	det
12	Time	Time	NNP	MISC	13	compound
13	Charter	Charter	NNP	MISC	9	nmod
14	was	be	VBD	O	15	auxpass
15	made	make	VBN	O	4	acl:relcl
16	by	by	IN	O	17	case
17	way	way	NN	O	15	nmod
18	of	of	IN	O	21	case
19	a	a	DT	O	21	det
20	``	``	``	O	21	punct
21	Notice	Notice	NNP	O	17	nmod
22	of	of	IN	O	23	case
23	Assignment	Assignment	NNP	O	21	nmod
24	of	of	IN	O	30	case
25	Time	Time	NNP	O	30	compound
26	Charter	Charter	NNP	O	30	compound
27	Party	Party	NNP	O	30	compound
28	 	 	NN	O	30	compound
29	-LSB-	-lsb-	-LRB-	O	30	punct
30	note	note	NN	O	23	nmod
31	:	:	:	O	4	punct
32	27	27	CD	NUMBER	4	conj
33	-RSB-	-rsb-	-RRB-	O	32	punct
34	dated	date	VBN	O	32	acl
35	22	22	CD	DATE	36	nummod
36	September	September	NNP	DATE	34	dobj
37	2008	2008	CD	DATE	36	nummod
38	from	from	IN	O	39	case
39	BGP	bgp	NN	O	36	nmod
40	to	to	TO	O	43	case
41	Nordic	nordic	JJ	ORGANIZATION	43	amod
42	Geo-Services	Geo-Services	NNP	ORGANIZATION	43	compound
43	Ltd	Ltd	NNP	ORGANIZATION	34	nmod
44	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	46	punct
45	``	``	``	O	46	punct
46	NGS	ngs	NN	O	43	appos
47	 	 	NN	O	46	dep
48	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	46	punct
49	,	,	,	O	43	punct
50	a	a	DT	O	52	det
51	wholly-owned	wholly-owned	JJ	O	52	amod
52	subsidiary	subsidiary	NN	O	43	appos
53	of	of	IN	O	55	case
54	Nordic	nordic	JJ	O	55	amod
55	Maritime	Maritime	NNP	O	52	nmod
56	,	,	,	O	43	punct
57	-LSB-	-lsb-	-LRB-	O	58	punct
58	note	note	NN	O	34	nmod
59	:	:	:	O	4	punct
60	28	28	CD	NUMBER	4	conj
61	-RSB-	-rsb-	-RRB-	O	60	punct
62	which	which	WDT	O	65	dobj
63	Morten	Morten	NNP	PERSON	65	nsubj
64	had	have	VBD	O	65	aux
65	incorporated	incorporate	VBN	O	60	acl:relcl
66	on	on	IN	O	67	case
67	10	10	CD	DATE	65	nmod
68	September	September	NNP	DATE	65	nmod:tmod
69	2008	2008	CD	DATE	68	nummod
70	-LSB-	-lsb-	-LRB-	O	71	punct
71	note	note	NN	O	65	nmod
72	:	:	:	O	4	punct
73	29	29	CD	NUMBER	4	conj
74	-RSB-	-rsb-	-RRB-	O	76	nsubj
75	to	to	TO	O	76	mark
76	take	take	VB	O	73	acl:relcl
77	over	over	RP	O	76	compound:prt
78	the	the	DT	O	80	det
79	Time	Time	NNP	ORGANIZATION	80	compound
80	Charter	Charter	NNP	ORGANIZATION	76	dobj
81	and	and	CC	O	4	cc
82	the	the	DT	O	85	det
83	seismic	seismic	JJ	O	85	amod
84	services	service	NNS	O	85	compound
85	agreement	agreement	NN	O	4	conj
86	from	from	IN	O	87	case
87	BGP	bgp	NN	O	85	nmod
88	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	-LSB-	-lsb-	-LRB-	O	2	punct
2	note	note	NN	O	29	nsubj
3	:	:	:	O	2	punct
4	30	30	CD	NUMBER	2	dep
5	-RSB-	-rsb-	-RRB-	O	8	punct
6	20	20	CD	NUMBER	7	compound
7	 	 	CD	NUMBER	8	nummod
8	 	 	NN	O	4	nmod
9	 	 	CD	NUMBER	8	compound
10	 	 	CD	NUMBER	8	compound
11	 	 	CD	NUMBER	8	compound
12	The	the	DT	O	14	det
13	material	material	NN	O	14	compound
14	terms	term	NNS	O	15	nsubj
15	were	be	VBD	O	4	acl:relcl
16	as	as	IN	O	17	mark
17	follows	follow	VBZ	O	15	advcl
18	:	:	:	O	4	punct
19	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	20	punct
20	a	a	LS	O	23	dep
21	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	20	punct
22	 	 	CD	NUMBER	23	nummod
23	 	 	CD	NUMBER	4	dep
24	 	 	NN	O	27	dep
25	 	 	CD	NUMBER	27	nummod
26	 	 	CD	NUMBER	27	nummod
27	BGP	bgp	NN	O	23	nmod
28	would	would	MD	O	29	aux
29	assign	assign	VB	O	0	ROOT
30	all	all	DT	O	33	dep
31	its	its	PRP$	O	33	nmod:poss
32	``	``	``	O	33	punct
33	rights	rights	NNS	O	29	nmod
34	,	,	,	O	33	punct
35	interest	interest	NN	O	33	conj
36	and	and	CC	O	33	cc
37	benefit	benefit	NN	O	33	conj
38	in	in	IN	O	33	nmod
39	and	and	CC	O	33	cc
40	under	under	IN	O	43	case
41	the	the	DT	O	43	det
42	Time	Time	NNP	MISC	43	compound
43	Charter	Charter	NNP	MISC	33	conj
44	 	 	CD	NUMBER	43	nummod
45	to	to	TO	O	46	case
46	NGS	NGS	NNP	O	29	nmod
47	.	.	.	O	29	punct

1	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	2	punct
2	b	b	NN	O	32	dep
3	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	2	punct
4	 	 	CD	NUMBER	5	compound
5	 	 	CD	NUMBER	6	nummod
6	 	 	NN	O	32	nsubj
7	 	 	CD	NUMBER	8	compound
8	 	 	CD	NUMBER	9	nummod
9	Pursuant	pursuant	NN	O	24	nsubj
10	to	to	TO	O	11	case
11	clause	clause	NN	O	9	nmod
12	17	17	CD	NUMBER	11	nummod
13	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	11	punct
14	a	a	DT	O	11	dep
15	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	11	punct
16	of	of	IN	O	21	case
17	the	the	DT	O	21	det
18	Time	Time	NNP	ORGANIZATION	21	compound
19	Charter	Charter	NNP	ORGANIZATION	21	compound
20	,	,	,	O	21	punct
21	BGP	BGP	NNP	ORGANIZATION	11	nmod
22	would	would	MD	O	24	aux
23	``	``	``	O	24	punct
24	remain	remain	VB	O	6	acl:relcl
25	liable	liable	JJ	O	24	xcomp
26	to	to	TO	O	29	case
27	-LSB-	-lsb-	-LRB-	O	29	punct
28	Nordic	nordic	JJ	O	29	amod
29	International	international	NN	O	25	nmod
30	-RSB-	-rsb-	-RRB-	O	32	punct
31	to	to	TO	O	32	mark
32	perform	perform	VB	O	0	ROOT
33	all	all	DT	O	32	dobj
34	-LSB-	-lsb-	-LRB-	O	37	punct
35	its	its	PRP$	O	37	nmod:poss
36	-RSB-	-rsb-	-RRB-	O	37	punct
37	obligations	obligation	NNS	O	33	nmod
38	and	and	CC	O	37	cc
39	liabilities	liability	NNS	O	37	conj
40	under	under	IN	O	44	case
41	the	the	DT	O	44	det
42	Time	Time	NNP	MISC	44	compound
43	Charter	Charter	NNP	MISC	44	compound
44	 	 	NN	MISC	32	nmod
45	.	.	.	O	32	punct

1	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	2	punct
2	c	c	NN	O	13	dep
3	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	2	punct
4	 	 	CD	NUMBER	5	compound
5	 	 	CD	NUMBER	6	nummod
6	 	 	NN	O	13	nsubj
7	 	 	CD	NUMBER	8	compound
8	 	 	CD	NUMBER	9	dep
9	NGS	ngs	NN	O	6	dep
10	would	would	MD	O	13	aux
11	be	be	VB	O	13	cop
12	``	``	``	O	13	punct
13	liable	liable	JJ	O	0	ROOT
14	to	to	TO	O	15	mark
15	pay	pay	VB	O	13	xcomp
16	to	to	TO	O	18	case
17	-LSB-	-lsb-	-LRB-	O	18	punct
18	BGP	bgp	NN	O	15	nmod
19	-RSB-	-rsb-	-RRB-	O	18	punct
20	,	,	,	O	13	punct
21	any	any	DT	O	25	nsubj
22	and	and	CC	O	21	cc
23	all	all	DT	O	24	det
24	charter	charter	NN	O	21	conj
25	hires	hire	VBZ	O	13	conj
26	and	and	CC	O	13	cc
27	any	any	DT	O	29	det
28	other	other	JJ	O	29	amod
29	monies	money	NNS	O	35	nsubj
30	payable	payable	JJ	O	29	amod
31	by	by	IN	O	33	case
32	-LSB-	-lsb-	-LRB-	O	33	punct
33	BGP	bgp	NN	O	30	nmod
34	-RSB-	-rsb-	-RRB-	O	35	punct
35	 	 	CD	NUMBER	13	conj
36	to	to	TO	O	39	case
37	-LSB-	-lsb-	-LRB-	O	39	punct
38	Nordic	nordic	JJ	O	39	amod
39	International	international	NN	O	35	nmod
40	-RSB-	-rsb-	-RRB-	O	39	punct
41	under	under	IN	O	45	case
42	the	the	DT	O	45	det
43	Time	Time	NNP	MISC	45	compound
44	Charter	Charter	NNP	MISC	45	compound
45	 	 	NN	MISC	35	nmod
46	.	.	.	O	13	punct

1	21	21	CD	NUMBER	2	compound
2	 	 	CD	NUMBER	3	nummod
3	 	 	NN	O	18	nsubj
4	 	 	CD	NUMBER	5	compound
5	 	 	CD	NUMBER	7	nummod
6	 	 	NN	O	7	compound
7	NGS	ngs	NN	O	8	nsubj
8	acknowledged	acknowledge	VBD	O	3	acl:relcl
9	the	the	DT	O	10	det
10	assignment	assignment	NN	O	8	dobj
11	by	by	IN	O	13	case
12	a	a	DT	O	13	det
13	letter	letter	NN	O	8	nmod
14	of	of	IN	O	17	case
15	the	the	DT	O	17	det
16	same	same	JJ	O	17	amod
17	date	date	NN	O	13	nmod
18	signed	sign	VBN	O	0	ROOT
19	by	by	IN	O	20	case
20	Morten	Morten	NNP	PERSON	18	nmod
21	in	in	IN	O	23	case
22	his	he	PRP$	O	23	nmod:poss
23	capacity	capacity	NN	O	18	nmod
24	as	as	IN	O	26	case
25	its	its	PRP$	O	26	nmod:poss
26	CEO	CEO	NNP	O	18	nmod
27	.	.	.	O	18	punct

1	-LSB-	-lsb-	-LRB-	O	2	punct
2	note	note	NN	O	0	ROOT
3	:	:	:	O	2	punct
4	31	31	CD	NUMBER	2	dep
5	-RSB-	-rsb-	-RRB-	O	8	punct
6	The	the	DT	O	8	det
7	legal	legal	JJ	O	8	amod
8	nature	nature	NN	O	4	nmod
9	of	of	IN	O	11	case
10	the	the	DT	O	11	det
11	MOA	MOA	NNP	ORGANIZATION	8	nmod
12	and	and	CC	O	11	cc
13	Notice	Notice	NNP	O	11	conj
14	of	of	IN	O	15	case
15	Assignment	Assignment	NNP	O	4	nmod
16	22	22	CD	NUMBER	17	compound
17	 	 	CD	NUMBER	18	nummod
18	 	 	NN	O	15	nmod
19	 	 	CD	NUMBER	18	compound
20	 	 	CD	NUMBER	18	compound
21	 	 	CD	NUMBER	18	compound
22	Before	before	IN	O	23	mark
23	going	go	VBG	O	29	advcl
24	further	further	RB	O	23	advmod
25	,	,	,	O	29	punct
26	it	it	PRP	O	29	nsubj
27	is	be	VBZ	O	29	cop
28	perhaps	perhaps	RB	O	29	advmod
29	useful	useful	JJ	O	18	dep
30	to	to	TO	O	32	mark
31	first	first	RB	ORDINAL	32	advmod
32	understand	understand	VB	O	29	xcomp
33	the	the	DT	O	36	det
34	true	true	JJ	O	36	amod
35	legal	legal	JJ	O	36	amod
36	nature	nature	NN	O	32	dobj
37	of	of	IN	O	39	case
38	the	the	DT	O	39	det
39	MOA	MOA	NNP	ORGANIZATION	36	nmod
40	and	and	CC	O	29	cc
41	the	the	DT	O	42	det
42	Notice	Notice	NNP	O	29	conj
43	of	of	IN	O	44	case
44	Assignment	Assignment	NNP	O	42	nmod
45	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	23	23	CD	NUMBER	2	compound
2	 	 	CD	NUMBER	3	nummod
3	 	 	NN	O	0	ROOT
4	 	 	CD	NUMBER	5	compound
5	 	 	CD	NUMBER	6	nummod
6	 	 	CD	NUMBER	3	dep
7	There	there	EX	O	8	expl
8	are	be	VBP	O	6	acl:relcl
9	two	two	CD	NUMBER	11	nummod
10	``	``	``	O	11	punct
11	assignments	assignment	NNS	O	8	nsubj
12	 	 	VBP	O	11	acl:relcl
13	in	in	IN	O	14	case
14	question	question	NN	O	12	nmod
15	here	here	RB	O	14	advmod
16	 	 	RB	O	14	advmod
17	one	one	CD	NUMBER	12	dobj
18	in	in	IN	O	19	case
19	relation	relation	NN	O	17	nmod
20	to	to	TO	O	23	case
21	the	the	DT	O	23	det
22	Time	Time	NNP	MISC	23	compound
23	Charter	Charter	NNP	MISC	12	nmod
24	,	,	,	O	23	punct
25	the	the	DT	O	33	det
26	other	other	JJ	O	33	amod
27	in	in	IN	O	28	case
28	relation	relation	NN	O	26	nmod
29	to	to	TO	O	32	case
30	the	the	DT	O	32	det
31	seismic	seismic	JJ	O	32	amod
32	services	service	NNS	O	26	nmod
33	agreement	agreement	NN	O	23	appos
34	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	On	on	IN	O	3	case
2	the	the	DT	O	3	det
3	face	face	NN	O	10	nmod
4	of	of	IN	O	7	case
5	the	the	DT	O	7	det
6	two	two	CD	NUMBER	7	nummod
7	assignments	assignment	NNS	O	3	nmod
8	,	,	,	O	10	punct
9	they	they	PRP	O	10	nsubj
10	appear	appear	VBP	O	0	ROOT
11	to	to	TO	O	12	mark
12	contradict	contradict	VB	O	10	xcomp
13	each	each	DT	O	14	det
14	other	other	JJ	O	12	dobj
15	.	.	.	O	10	punct

1	Under	under	IN	O	3	case
2	the	the	DT	O	3	det
3	MOA	MOA	NNP	ORGANIZATION	9	nmod
4	,	,	,	O	9	punct
5	BGP	BGP	NNP	O	9	nsubj
6	was	be	VBD	O	9	cop
7	purportedly	purportedly	RB	O	9	advmod
8	``	``	``	O	9	punct
9	relieved	relieved	JJ	O	0	ROOT
10	and	and	CC	O	9	cc
11	released	release	VBN	O	9	conj
12	of	of	IN	O	14	case
13	the	the	DT	O	14	det
14	obligations	obligation	NNS	O	11	nmod
15	under	under	IN	O	19	case
16	the	the	DT	O	19	det
17	Time	Time	NNP	MISC	19	compound
18	Charter	Charter	NNP	MISC	19	compound
19	 	 	NN	O	11	nmod
20	while	while	IN	O	30	mark
21	under	under	IN	O	23	case
22	the	the	DT	O	23	det
23	Notice	Notice	NNP	O	30	nmod
24	of	of	IN	O	25	case
25	Assignment	Assignment	NNP	O	23	nmod
26	,	,	,	O	30	punct
27	BGP	BGP	NNP	ORGANIZATION	30	nsubj
28	would	would	MD	O	30	aux
29	``	``	``	O	30	punct
30	remain	remain	VB	O	11	advcl
31	liable	liable	JJ	O	30	xcomp
32	to	to	TO	O	35	case
33	-LSB-	-lsb-	-LRB-	O	35	punct
34	Nordic	nordic	JJ	O	35	amod
35	International	international	NN	O	31	nmod
36	-RSB-	-rsb-	-RRB-	O	35	punct
37	to	to	TO	O	38	mark
38	perform	perform	VB	O	30	xcomp
39	all	all	DT	O	38	dobj
40	-LSB-	-lsb-	-LRB-	O	43	punct
41	its	its	PRP$	O	43	nmod:poss
42	-RSB-	-rsb-	-RRB-	O	43	punct
43	obligations	obligation	NNS	O	39	nmod
44	and	and	CC	O	43	cc
45	liabilities	liability	NNS	O	43	conj
46	under	under	IN	O	50	case
47	the	the	DT	O	50	det
48	Time	Time	NNP	MISC	50	compound
49	Charter	Charter	NNP	MISC	50	compound
50	 	 	NN	MISC	38	nmod
51	.	.	.	O	9	punct

1	24	24	CD	NUMBER	2	compound
2	 	 	CD	NUMBER	3	nummod
3	 	 	NN	O	14	ccomp
4	 	 	CD	NUMBER	5	compound
5	 	 	CD	NUMBER	3	amod
6	 	 	CD	NUMBER	5	dep
7	In	in	IN	O	9	case
8	my	my	PRP$	O	9	nmod:poss
9	view	view	NN	O	6	nmod
10	,	,	,	O	14	punct
11	it	it	PRP	O	14	nsubj
12	is	be	VBZ	O	14	cop
13	a	a	DT	O	14	det
14	misnomer	misnomer	NN	O	0	ROOT
15	to	to	TO	O	16	mark
16	describe	describe	VB	O	14	acl
17	the	the	DT	O	18	det
18	Notice	Notice	NNP	O	16	dobj
19	of	of	IN	O	20	case
20	Assignment	Assignment	NNP	O	18	nmod
21	as	as	IN	O	25	case
22	an	a	DT	O	25	det
23	``	``	``	O	25	punct
24	assignment	assignment	NN	O	25	compound
25	 	 	NN	O	16	nmod
26	of	of	IN	O	29	case
27	the	the	DT	O	29	det
28	Time	Time	NNP	O	29	compound
29	Charter	Charter	NNP	O	25	nmod
30	.	.	.	O	14	punct

1	It	it	PRP	O	3	nsubj
2	is	be	VBZ	O	3	cop
3	incontrovertible	incontrovertible	JJ	O	0	ROOT
4	that	that	IN	O	13	mark
5	only	only	RB	O	7	advmod
6	the	the	DT	O	7	det
7	benefits	benefit	NNS	O	13	nsubjpass
8	of	of	IN	O	10	case
9	a	a	DT	O	10	det
10	contract	contract	NN	O	7	nmod
11	can	can	MD	O	13	aux
12	be	be	VB	O	13	auxpass
13	assigned	assign	VBN	O	3	ccomp
14	,	,	,	O	3	punct
15	not	not	RB	O	3	dep
16	the	the	DT	O	17	det
17	burdens	burden	NNS	O	15	dep
18	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	It	it	PRP	O	4	nsubj
2	was	be	VBD	O	4	cop
3	Nordic	nordic	JJ	MISC	4	amod
4	International	International	NNP	MISC	0	ROOT
5	who	who	WP	O	12	nsubj
6	,	,	,	O	12	punct
7	under	under	IN	O	10	case
8	the	the	DT	O	10	det
9	Time	Time	NNP	MISC	10	compound
10	Charter	Charter	NNP	MISC	12	nmod
11	,	,	,	O	12	punct
12	had	have	VBD	O	4	acl:relcl
13	the	the	DT	O	14	det
14	right	right	NN	O	12	dobj
15	to	to	TO	O	16	mark
16	receive	receive	VB	O	14	acl
17	payment	payment	NN	O	16	dobj
18	of	of	IN	O	21	case
19	the	the	DT	O	21	det
20	charter	charter	NN	O	21	compound
21	hire	hire	NN	O	17	nmod
22	from	from	IN	O	23	case
23	BGP	bgp	NN	O	16	nmod
24	.	.	.	O	4	punct

1	Hence	hence	RB	O	21	advmod
2	,	,	,	O	21	punct
3	if	if	IN	O	5	mark
4	there	there	EX	O	5	expl
5	is	be	VBZ	O	21	advcl
6	any	any	DT	O	7	det
7	assignment	assignment	NN	O	5	nsubj
8	of	of	IN	O	11	case
9	the	the	DT	O	11	det
10	Time	Time	NNP	ORGANIZATION	11	compound
11	Charter	Charter	NNP	ORGANIZATION	7	nmod
12	to	to	TO	O	13	mark
13	speak	speak	VB	O	7	acl
14	of	of	IN	O	13	nmod
15	,	,	,	O	21	punct
16	it	it	PRP	O	21	nsubj
17	would	would	MD	O	21	aux
18	be	be	VB	O	21	cop
19	by	by	IN	O	21	case
20	Nordic	nordic	JJ	ORGANIZATION	21	amod
21	International	International	NNP	ORGANIZATION	0	ROOT
22	and	and	CC	O	21	cc
23	not	not	RB	O	21	conj
24	BGP	bgp	NN	O	26	nsubj
25	to	to	TO	O	26	mark
26	begin	begin	VB	O	21	dep
27	with	with	IN	O	26	nmod
28	.	.	.	O	21	punct

1	Nordic	nordic	JJ	MISC	2	amod
2	International	International	NNP	MISC	3	nsubj
3	was	be	VBD	O	0	ROOT
4	,	,	,	O	3	punct
5	however	however	RB	O	3	parataxis
6	,	,	,	O	5	punct
7	neither	neither	CC	O	5	dep
8	a	a	DT	O	9	det
9	party	party	NN	O	5	conj
10	to	to	TO	O	12	case
11	the	the	DT	O	12	det
12	MOA	MOA	NNP	O	9	nmod
13	nor	nor	CC	O	12	cc
14	the	the	DT	O	15	det
15	Notice	Notice	NNP	O	12	conj
16	of	of	IN	O	17	case
17	Assignment	Assignment	NNP	O	15	nmod
18	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	25	25	CD	NUMBER	2	compound
2	 	 	CD	NUMBER	12	nsubj
3	 	 	NN	O	7	nummod
4	 	 	CD	NUMBER	3	compound
5	 	 	CD	NUMBER	3	compound
6	 	 	CD	NUMBER	3	compound
7	BGP	bgp	NN	O	8	nsubj
8	did	do	VBD	O	2	acl:relcl
9	,	,	,	O	12	punct
10	however	however	RB	O	12	advmod
11	,	,	,	O	12	punct
12	have	have	VBP	O	0	ROOT
13	the	the	DT	O	14	det
14	option	option	NN	O	12	dobj
15	,	,	,	O	18	punct
16	under	under	IN	O	17	case
17	clause	clause	NN	O	18	nmod
18	17	17	CD	NUMBER	14	dep
19	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	18	punct
20	a	a	DT	O	18	dep
21	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	18	punct
22	of	of	IN	O	25	case
23	the	the	DT	O	25	det
24	Time	Time	NNP	MISC	25	compound
25	Charter	Charter	NNP	MISC	18	nmod
26	,	,	,	O	18	punct
27	of	of	IN	O	29	case
28	``	``	``	O	29	punct
29	subletting	sublet	VBG	O	18	dep
30	,	,	,	O	29	punct
31	assigning	assign	VBG	O	29	conj
32	or	or	CC	O	29	cc
33	loaning	loan	VBG	O	29	conj
34	the	the	DT	O	35	det
35	Vessel	vessel	NN	O	29	dobj
36	to	to	TO	O	43	mark
37	any	any	DT	O	38	det
38	person	person	NN	O	43	nsubj
39	or	or	CC	O	38	cc
40	company	company	NN	O	38	conj
41	 	 	CD	NUMBER	40	nummod
42	not	not	RB	O	43	neg
43	competing	compete	VBG	O	35	acl
44	with	with	IN	O	47	case
45	-LSB-	-lsb-	-LRB-	O	47	punct
46	Nordic	nordic	JJ	MISC	47	amod
47	International	international	NN	MISC	43	nmod
48	-RSB-	-rsb-	-RRB-	O	50	punct
49	,	,	,	O	50	punct
50	subject	subject	JJ	O	47	amod
51	to	to	TO	O	56	mark
52	-LSB-	-lsb-	-LRB-	O	56	punct
53	Nordic	nordic	JJ	O	56	amod
54	International	international	JJ	O	56	amod
55	 	 	NN	O	56	compound
56	s	s	NNS	O	29	xcomp
57	-RSB-	-rsb-	-RRB-	O	14	punct
58	prior	prior	RB	O	14	advmod
59	approval	approval	NN	O	14	dep
60	``	``	``	O	66	punct
61	which	which	WDT	O	66	nsubjpass
62	shall	shall	MD	O	66	aux
63	not	not	RB	O	66	neg
64	be	be	VB	O	66	auxpass
65	unreasonably	unreasonably	RB	O	66	advmod
66	withheld	withhold	VBN	O	59	acl:relcl
67	,	,	,	O	66	punct
68	upon	upon	IN	O	69	mark
69	giving	give	VBG	O	66	advcl
70	notice	notice	NN	O	69	dobj
71	in	in	IN	O	72	mark
72	writing	write	VBG	O	69	advcl
73	to	to	TO	O	76	case
74	-LSB-	-lsb-	-LRB-	O	76	punct
75	Nordic	nordic	JJ	O	76	amod
76	International	international	NN	O	72	nmod
77	-RSB-	-rsb-	-RRB-	O	78	punct
78	 	 	NN	O	76	nmod
79	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	80	punct
80	emphasis	emphasis	NN	O	59	dep
81	added	add	VBN	O	80	acl
82	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	80	punct
83	.	.	.	O	12	punct

1	This	this	DT	O	3	nsubjpass
2	was	be	VBD	O	3	auxpass
3	provided	provide	VBN	O	0	ROOT
4	that	that	IN	O	6	mark
5	BGP	bgp	NN	O	6	nsubj
6	remained	remain	VBD	O	3	ccomp
7	liable	liable	JJ	O	6	xcomp
8	``	``	``	O	11	punct
9	for	for	IN	O	11	case
10	the	the	DT	O	11	det
11	performance	performance	NN	O	6	nmod
12	of	of	IN	O	16	case
13	the	the	DT	O	16	det
14	-LSB-	-lsb-	-LRB-	O	16	punct
15	Time	Time	NNP	O	16	compound
16	Charter	Charter	NNP	O	11	nmod
17	-RSB-	-rsb-	-RRB-	O	18	punct
18	 	 	CD	NUMBER	16	nmod
19	to	to	TO	O	21	case
20	Nordic	nordic	JJ	O	21	amod
21	International	International	NNP	O	6	nmod
22	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	So	so	IN	O	27	dep
2	what	what	WDT	O	7	dobj
3	BGP	bgp	NN	O	7	nsubj
4	had	have	VBD	O	7	aux
5	was	be	VBD	O	7	cop
6	the	the	DT	O	7	det
7	right	right	NN	O	27	advcl
8	to	to	TO	O	9	mark
9	assign	assign	VB	O	7	acl
10	its	its	PRP$	O	11	nmod:poss
11	use	use	NN	O	9	dobj
12	of	of	IN	O	14	case
13	the	the	DT	O	14	det
14	vessel	vessel	NN	O	11	nmod
15	,	,	,	O	14	punct
16	not	not	RB	O	19	neg
17	the	the	DT	O	19	det
18	Time	Time	NNP	MISC	19	compound
19	Charter	Charter	NNP	MISC	14	appos
20	itself	itself	PRP	O	14	advmod
21	;	;	:	O	11	punct
22	the	the	DT	O	23	det
23	property	property	NN	O	11	dep
24	,	,	,	O	27	punct
25	not	not	RB	O	26	neg
26	the	the	DT	O	27	nsubj
27	chose	choose	VBD	O	0	ROOT
28	in	in	IN	O	29	case
29	action	action	NN	O	27	nmod
30	.	.	.	O	27	punct

1	As	as	IN	O	5	mark
2	Morten	Morten	NNP	PERSON	3	compound
3	 	 	NNP	O	5	nsubj
4	s	be	VBZ	O	5	cop
5	email	email	NN	O	18	advcl
6	to	to	TO	O	7	case
7	BGP	BGP	NNP	O	5	nmod
8	indicated	indicate	VBD	O	7	acl:relcl
9	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	10	punct
10	see	see	VB	O	7	dep
11	-LSB-	-lsb-	-LRB-	O	12	punct
12	12	12	CD	NUMBER	10	dobj
13	-RSB-	-rsb-	-RRB-	O	12	punct
14	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	10	punct
15	,	,	,	O	18	punct
16	BGP	bgp	NN	O	18	nsubj
17	was	be	VBD	O	18	aux
18	transferring	transfer	VBG	O	0	ROOT
19	the	the	DT	O	20	det
20	operation	operation	NN	O	18	dobj
21	of	of	IN	O	23	case
22	the	the	DT	O	23	det
23	Vessel	vessel	NN	O	20	nmod
24	to	to	TO	O	26	case
25	Nordic	nordic	JJ	O	26	amod
26	Maritime	Maritime	NNP	O	18	nmod
27	.	.	.	O	18	punct

1	26	26	CD	NUMBER	2	compound
2	 	 	CD	NUMBER	3	nummod
3	 	 	NN	O	16	nsubj
4	 	 	CD	NUMBER	5	compound
5	 	 	CD	NUMBER	3	amod
6	 	 	CD	NUMBER	5	dep
7	As	as	IN	O	12	case
8	for	for	IN	O	12	case
9	the	the	DT	O	12	det
10	seismic	seismic	JJ	O	12	amod
11	services	service	NNS	O	12	compound
12	agreement	agreement	NN	O	6	nmod
13	,	,	,	O	12	punct
14	BGP	bgp	NN	ORGANIZATION	12	appos
15	did	do	VBD	O	16	aux
16	assign	assign	VB	O	0	ROOT
17	to	to	TO	O	18	mark
18	NGS	ng	VB	O	16	xcomp
19	its	its	PRP$	O	20	nmod:poss
20	right	right	NN	O	18	dobj
21	to	to	TO	O	22	mark
22	receive	receive	VB	O	20	acl
23	the	the	DT	O	26	det
24	seismic	seismic	JJ	O	26	amod
25	services	service	NNS	O	26	compound
26	fees	fee	NNS	O	22	dobj
27	from	from	IN	O	28	case
28	TGS	tgs	NN	ORGANIZATION	22	nmod
29	.	.	.	O	16	punct

1	That	that	DT	O	4	nsubj
2	was	be	VBD	O	4	cop
3	an	a	DT	O	4	det
4	assignment	assignment	NN	O	0	ROOT
5	of	of	IN	O	9	case
6	a	a	DT	O	9	det
7	chose	choose	VBN	O	9	amod
8	in	in	IN	O	7	nmod
9	action	action	NN	O	4	nmod
10	.	.	.	O	4	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	2	det
2	Notice	Notice	NNP	ORGANIZATION	5	nsubj
3	of	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	4	case
4	Assignment	Assignment	NNP	ORGANIZATION	2	nmod
5	stated	state	VBD	O	0	ROOT
6	that	that	IN	O	11	mark
7	its	its	PRP$	O	8	nmod:poss
8	validity	validity	NN	O	11	nsubjpass
9	would	would	MD	O	11	aux
10	be	be	VB	O	11	auxpass
11	governed	govern	VBN	O	5	ccomp
12	by	by	IN	O	14	case
13	the	the	DT	O	14	det
14	laws	law	NNS	O	11	nmod
15	of	of	IN	O	18	case
16	the	the	DT	O	18	det
17	United	United	NNP	LOCATION	18	compound
18	Kingdom	Kingdom	NNP	LOCATION	14	nmod
19	.	.	.	O	5	punct

1	Both	both	DT	O	2	det
2	parties	party	NNS	O	3	nsubj
3	referred	refer	VBD	O	7	dep
4	me	I	PRP	O	3	dobj
5	to	to	TO	O	6	case
6	s	s	NNS	O	3	nmod
7	 	 	VBP	O	0	ROOT
8	136	136	CD	NUMBER	7	dobj
9	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	10	punct
10	1	1	CD	NUMBER	8	appos
11	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	10	punct
12	of	of	IN	O	15	case
13	the	the	DT	O	15	det
14	English	English	NNP	MISC	15	compound
15	Law	law	NN	MISC	8	nmod
16	of	of	IN	MISC	18	case
17	Property	Property	NNP	MISC	18	compound
18	Act	Act	NNP	MISC	15	nmod
19	1925	1925	CD	DATE	7	nsubj
20	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	21	punct
21	c	c	NN	O	19	appos
22	20	20	CD	NUMBER	21	nummod
23	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	21	punct
24	-LSB-	-lsb-	-LRB-	O	25	punct
25	note	note	NN	O	19	dep
26	:	:	:	O	25	punct
27	32	32	CD	NUMBER	25	dep
28	-RSB-	-rsb-	-RRB-	O	27	punct
29	which	which	WDT	O	36	nsubj
30	is	be	VBZ	O	36	cop
31	in	in	IN	O	33	case
32	pari	pari	NN	O	33	compound
33	materia	materia	NN	O	36	nmod
34	with	with	IN	O	35	case
35	s	s	NNS	O	33	nmod
36	4	4	CD	NUMBER	27	acl:relcl
37	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	38	punct
38	8	8	CD	NUMBER	36	appos
39	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	38	punct
40	of	of	IN	O	44	case
41	the	the	DT	O	44	det
42	Civil	Civil	NNP	MISC	44	compound
43	Law	Law	NNP	MISC	44	compound
44	Act	Act	NNP	MISC	36	nmod
45	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	46	punct
46	Cap	Cap	NNP	O	27	dep
47	43	43	CD	NUMBER	46	nummod
48	,	,	,	O	46	punct
49	1999	1999	CD	DATE	51	nummod
50	Rev	rev	NN	O	51	compound
51	Ed	Ed	NNP	O	46	appos
52	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	46	punct
53	.	.	.	O	7	punct

1	Under	under	IN	O	3	case
2	these	these	DT	O	3	det
3	provisions	provision	NNS	O	11	nmod
4	,	,	,	O	11	punct
5	express	express	VBP	O	11	csubjpass
6	notice	notice	NN	O	5	dobj
7	in	in	IN	O	8	mark
8	writing	write	VBG	O	5	advcl
9	must	must	MD	O	11	aux
10	be	be	VB	O	11	auxpass
11	given	give	VBN	O	0	ROOT
12	to	to	TO	O	15	case
13	the	the	DT	O	15	det
14	``	``	``	O	15	punct
15	debtor	debtor	NN	O	11	nmod
16	 	 	CD	NUMBER	24	dobj
17	from	from	IN	O	18	case
18	whom	whom	WP	O	16	nmod
19	the	the	DT	O	20	det
20	assignor	assignor	NN	O	24	nsubjpass
21	would	would	MD	O	24	aux
22	have	have	VB	O	24	aux
23	been	be	VBN	O	24	auxpass
24	entitled	entitle	VBN	O	15	acl:relcl
25	to	to	TO	O	26	mark
26	receive	receive	VB	O	24	xcomp
27	or	or	CC	O	26	cc
28	claim	claim	VB	O	26	conj
29	-LSB-	-lsb-	-LRB-	O	32	punct
30	the	the	DT	O	32	det
31	-RSB-	-rsb-	-RRB-	O	32	punct
32	debt	debt	NN	O	26	nmod
33	or	or	CC	O	24	cc
34	chose	choose	VBD	O	24	conj
35	in	in	IN	O	36	case
36	action	action	NN	O	34	nmod
37	 	 	CD	NUMBER	36	nummod
38	.	.	.	O	11	punct

1	BGP	bgp	NN	O	4	nsubj
2	is	be	VBZ	O	4	cop
3	the	the	DT	O	4	det
4	assignor	assignor	NN	O	0	ROOT
5	while	while	IN	O	9	mark
6	TGS	tgs	NN	ORGANIZATION	9	nsubj
7	is	be	VBZ	O	9	cop
8	the	the	DT	O	9	det
9	debtor	debtor	NN	O	4	advcl
10	.	.	.	O	4	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	2	det
2	Notice	Notice	NNP	O	9	nsubj
3	of	of	IN	O	4	case
4	Assignment	Assignment	NNP	O	2	nmod
5	was	be	VBD	O	4	acl
6	,	,	,	O	9	punct
7	however	however	RB	O	9	advmod
8	,	,	,	O	9	punct
9	addressed	address	VBD	O	0	ROOT
10	from	from	IN	O	11	case
11	BGP	bgp	NN	O	9	nmod
12	to	to	TO	O	13	case
13	NGS	ngs	NN	O	9	advcl
14	,	,	,	O	13	punct
15	not	not	RB	O	17	neg
16	to	to	TO	O	17	case
17	TGS	TGS	NNP	ORGANIZATION	13	nmod
18	.	.	.	O	9	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	2	det
2	MOA	MOA	NNP	O	10	nsubjpass
3	,	,	,	O	2	punct
4	on	on	IN	O	7	case
5	the	the	DT	O	7	det
6	other	other	JJ	O	7	amod
7	hand	hand	NN	O	2	nmod
8	,	,	,	O	2	punct
9	was	be	VBD	O	10	auxpass
10	signed	sign	VBN	O	0	ROOT
11	both	both	CC	O	13	dep
12	by	by	IN	O	13	case
13	BGP	bgp	NN	O	10	nmod
14	and	and	CC	O	13	cc
15	TGS	tgs	NN	ORGANIZATION	13	conj
16	.	.	.	O	10	punct

1	It	it	PRP	O	4	nsubj
2	may	may	MD	O	4	aux
3	well	well	RB	O	4	advmod
4	be	be	VB	O	0	ROOT
5	that	that	IN	O	8	mark
6	only	only	RB	O	8	advmod
7	the	the	DT	O	8	det
8	MOA	MOA	NNP	O	4	dep
9	,	,	,	O	4	punct
10	and	and	CC	O	4	cc
11	not	not	RB	O	16	neg
12	the	the	DT	O	13	det
13	Notice	Notice	NNP	O	16	nsubj
14	of	of	IN	O	15	case
15	Assignment	Assignment	NNP	O	13	nmod
16	constituted	constitute	VBD	O	4	conj
17	the	the	DT	O	21	nsubj
18	statutorily	statutorily	RB	O	19	advmod
19	required	require	VBN	O	17	acl
20	``	``	``	O	21	punct
21	express	express	VBP	O	16	ccomp
22	notice	notice	NN	O	21	dobj
23	in	in	IN	O	24	mark
24	writing	write	VBG	O	21	advcl
25	 	 	CD	NUMBER	24	dobj
26	to	to	TO	O	28	case
27	the	the	DT	O	28	det
28	debtor	debtor	NN	O	24	nmod
29	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	30	punct
30	TGS	tgs	NN	ORGANIZATION	28	appos
31	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	30	punct
32	.	.	.	O	4	punct

1	That	that	DT	O	8	nsubj
2	,	,	,	O	8	punct
3	however	however	RB	O	8	advmod
4	,	,	,	O	8	punct
5	is	be	VBZ	O	8	cop
6	not	not	RB	O	8	neg
7	a	a	DT	O	8	det
8	matter	matter	NN	O	0	ROOT
9	I	I	PRP	O	10	nsubj
10	have	have	VBP	O	8	acl:relcl
11	to	to	TO	O	12	mark
12	decide	decide	VB	O	10	xcomp
13	.	.	.	O	8	punct

1	I	I	PRP	O	22	nsubj
2	am	be	VBP	O	22	aux
3	not	not	RB	O	22	neg
4	,	,	,	O	22	punct
5	for	for	IN	O	22	mark
6	the	the	DT	O	7	det
7	purposes	purpose	NNS	O	22	nsubj
8	of	of	IN	O	10	case
9	this	this	DT	O	10	det
10	case	case	NN	O	7	nmod
11	,	,	,	O	10	punct
12	concerned	concern	VBN	O	10	acl
13	with	with	IN	O	15	case
14	the	the	DT	O	15	det
15	validity	validity	NN	O	12	nmod
16	of	of	IN	O	17	case
17	any	any	DT	O	15	nmod
18	of	of	IN	O	19	case
19	these	these	DT	O	17	nmod
20	``	``	``	O	19	punct
21	assignments	assignment	NNS	O	19	dep
22	 	 	VBP	O	0	ROOT
23	.	.	.	O	22	punct

1	Instead	instead	RB	O	6	advmod
2	,	,	,	O	6	punct
3	I	I	PRP	O	6	nsubjpass
4	am	be	VBP	O	6	auxpass
5	only	only	RB	O	6	advmod
6	concerned	concern	VBN	O	0	ROOT
7	with	with	IN	O	18	mark
8	whether	whether	IN	O	18	mark
9	Morten	Morten	NNP	PERSON	11	compound
10	 	 	CD	PERSON	11	nummod
11	s	s	NNS	O	18	nsubj
12	structuring	structure	VBG	O	11	acl
13	of	of	IN	O	15	case
14	these	these	DT	O	15	det
15	arrangements	arrangement	NNS	O	12	nmod
16	was	be	VBD	O	18	cop
17	in	in	IN	O	18	case
18	breach	breach	NN	O	6	advcl
19	of	of	IN	O	21	case
20	his	he	PRP$	O	21	nmod:poss
21	duties	duty	NNS	O	18	nmod
22	as	as	IN	O	24	case
23	a	a	DT	O	24	det
24	director	director	NN	O	18	nmod
25	of	of	IN	O	27	case
26	Nordic	nordic	JJ	O	27	amod
27	International	International	NNP	O	24	nmod
28	.	.	.	O	6	punct

1	27	27	CD	NUMBER	2	compound
2	 	 	CD	NUMBER	3	nummod
3	 	 	NN	O	12	nsubj
4	 	 	CD	NUMBER	5	compound
5	 	 	CD	NUMBER	3	amod
6	 	 	CD	NUMBER	5	dep
7	Since	since	IN	O	9	case
8	both	both	DT	O	9	det
9	parties	party	NNS	O	6	nmod
10	have	have	VBP	O	12	aux
11	consistently	consistently	RB	O	12	advmod
12	used	use	VBN	O	27	ccomp
13	the	the	DT	O	17	det
14	term	term	NN	O	17	compound
15	``	``	``	O	17	punct
16	assignment	assignment	NN	O	17	compound
17	 	 	NN	O	12	dobj
18	in	in	IN	O	20	case
19	their	they	PRP$	O	20	nmod:poss
20	pleadings	pleading	NNS	O	12	nmod
21	and	and	CC	O	20	cc
22	submissions	submission	NNS	O	20	conj
23	,	,	,	O	27	punct
24	this	this	DT	O	25	det
25	judgment	judgment	NN	O	27	nsubj
26	will	will	MD	O	27	aux
27	continue	continue	VB	O	0	ROOT
28	to	to	TO	O	29	mark
29	use	use	VB	O	27	xcomp
30	``	``	``	O	29	punct
31	assignment	assignment	NN	O	29	dobj
32	 	 	CD	NUMBER	31	nummod
33	to	to	TO	O	34	mark
34	refer	refer	VB	O	29	advcl
35	to	to	TO	O	37	case
36	the	the	DT	O	37	det
37	arrangement	arrangement	NN	O	34	nmod
38	involving	involve	VBG	O	37	acl
39	BGP	bgp	NN	O	38	dobj
40	 	 	CD	NUMBER	41	nummod
41	s	s	NNS	O	42	nmod:npmod
42	purported	purported	JJ	O	39	amod
43	``	``	``	O	39	punct
44	assignment	assignment	NN	O	45	compound
45	 	 	NN	O	39	dep
46	of	of	IN	O	49	case
47	the	the	DT	O	49	det
48	Time	Time	NNP	O	49	compound
49	Charter	Charter	NNP	O	45	nmod
50	as	as	RB	O	39	cc
51	well	well	RB	O	50	mwe
52	as	as	IN	O	50	mwe
53	the	the	DT	O	54	det
54	benefit	benefit	NN	O	39	conj
55	of	of	IN	O	59	case
56	the	the	DT	O	59	det
57	seismic	seismic	JJ	O	59	amod
58	services	service	NNS	O	59	compound
59	agreement	agreement	NN	O	54	nmod
60	to	to	TO	O	61	case
61	NGS	NGS	NNP	O	38	nmod
62	,	,	,	O	38	punct
63	subject	subject	JJ	O	38	xcomp
64	to	to	TO	O	66	case
65	the	the	DT	O	66	det
66	caveats	caveat	NNS	O	63	nmod
67	about	about	IN	O	69	case
68	the	the	DT	O	69	det
69	use	use	NN	O	66	nmod
70	of	of	IN	O	73	case
71	this	this	DT	O	73	det
72	descriptive	descriptive	JJ	O	73	amod
73	term	term	NN	O	69	nmod
74	as	as	IN	O	75	mark
75	mentioned	mention	VBN	O	27	advcl
76	above	above	IN	O	75	nmod
77	.	.	.	O	27	punct

1	28	28	CD	NUMBER	2	nummod
2	 	 	CD	NUMBER	15	nsubj
3	 	 	NN	O	2	dep
4	 	 	CD	NUMBER	3	nummod
5	 	 	CD	NUMBER	6	compound
6	 	 	CD	NUMBER	9	nummod
7	The	the	DT	O	9	det
8	net	net	JJ	O	9	amod
9	effect	effect	NN	O	2	dep
10	of	of	IN	O	14	case
11	the	the	DT	O	14	det
12	two	two	CD	NUMBER	14	nummod
13	purported	purported	JJ	O	14	amod
14	assignments	assignment	NNS	O	9	nmod
15	is	be	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
16	that	that	IN	O	19	mark
17	BGP	bgp	NN	O	19	nsubjpass
18	was	be	VBD	O	19	auxpass
19	taken	take	VBN	O	15	ccomp
20	out	out	IN	O	23	case
21	of	of	IN	O	23	amod
22	the	the	DT	O	23	det
23	equation	equation	NN	O	19	nmod
24	vis	vis	FW	O	23	dep
25	-	-	:	O	19	punct
26	 	 	SYM	O	29	dep
27	-	-	:	O	29	punct
28	vis	vis	FW	O	29	compound
29	TGS	tgs	FW	ORGANIZATION	19	dep
30	but	but	CC	O	31	cc
31	remained	remain	VBD	O	29	dep
32	liable	liable	JJ	O	31	xcomp
33	to	to	TO	O	35	case
34	Nordic	nordic	JJ	O	35	amod
35	International	International	NNP	O	32	nmod
36	for	for	IN	O	39	case
37	the	the	DT	O	39	det
38	charter	charter	NN	O	39	compound
39	hire	hire	NN	O	31	nmod
40	under	under	IN	O	44	case
41	a	a	DT	O	44	det
42	rather	rather	RB	O	43	advmod
43	convoluted	convoluted	JJ	O	44	amod
44	arrangement	arrangement	NN	O	31	nmod
45	.	.	.	O	29	punct

1	This	this	DT	O	2	det
2	arrangement	arrangement	NN	O	5	nsubj
3	has	have	VBZ	O	5	aux
4	since	since	IN	O	5	advmod
5	become	become	VBN	O	0	ROOT
6	a	a	DT	O	7	det
7	source	source	NN	O	5	xcomp
8	of	of	IN	O	9	case
9	dispute	dispute	NN	O	7	nmod
10	between	between	IN	O	12	case
11	Nordic	nordic	JJ	ORGANIZATION	12	amod
12	International	International	NNP	ORGANIZATION	9	nmod
13	and	and	CC	O	12	cc
14	BGP	BGP	NNP	O	12	conj
15	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	16	punct
16	see	see	VB	O	5	parataxis
17	-LSB-	-lsb-	-LRB-	O	18	punct
18	37	37	CD	NUMBER	16	nmod
19	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	16	punct
20	.	.	.	O	5	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	2	det
2	reaction	reaction	NN	O	29	nsubjpass
3	of	of	IN	O	5	case
4	Nordic	nordic	JJ	O	5	amod
5	International	International	NNP	O	2	nmod
6	to	to	TO	O	9	case
7	the	the	DT	O	9	det
8	purported	purported	JJ	O	9	amod
9	assignments	assignment	NNS	O	2	nmod
10	29	29	CD	NUMBER	11	compound
11	 	 	CD	NUMBER	12	nummod
12	 	 	NN	O	9	nmod
13	 	 	CD	NUMBER	14	compound
14	 	 	CD	NUMBER	15	nummod
15	 	 	CD	NUMBER	12	dep
16	According	accord	VBG	O	19	case
17	to	to	TO	O	16	mwe
18	Nordic	nordic	JJ	ORGANIZATION	19	amod
19	International	International	NNP	ORGANIZATION	15	nmod
20	,	,	,	O	19	punct
21	the	the	DT	O	23	det
22	purported	purported	JJ	O	23	amod
23	assignment	assignment	NN	O	19	appos
24	of	of	IN	O	27	case
25	the	the	DT	O	27	det
26	Time	Time	NNP	MISC	27	compound
27	Charter	Charter	NNP	MISC	23	nmod
28	was	be	VBD	O	29	auxpass
29	made	make	VBN	O	0	ROOT
30	by	by	IN	O	31	case
31	way	way	NN	O	29	nmod
32	of	of	IN	O	34	case
33	the	the	DT	O	34	det
34	Notice	Notice	NNP	ORGANIZATION	31	nmod
35	of	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	36	case
36	Assignment	Assignment	NNP	ORGANIZATION	34	nmod
37	dated	dated	JJ	O	36	amod
38	22	22	CD	DATE	37	nmod:tmod
39	September	September	NNP	DATE	29	nmod:tmod
40	2008	2008	CD	DATE	39	nummod
41	,	,	,	O	29	punct
42	and	and	CC	O	29	cc
43	Morten	Morten	NNP	PERSON	46	nsubj
44	did	do	VBD	O	46	aux
45	not	not	RB	O	46	neg
46	inform	inform	VB	O	29	conj
47	it	it	PRP	O	46	dobj
48	of	of	IN	O	51	case
49	the	the	DT	O	51	det
50	purported	purported	JJ	O	51	amod
51	assignment	assignment	NN	O	46	nmod
52	before	before	IN	O	55	mark
53	it	it	PRP	O	55	nsubjpass
54	was	be	VBD	O	55	auxpass
55	executed	execute	VBN	O	46	advcl
56	.	.	.	O	29	punct

1	-LSB-	-lsb-	-LRB-	O	2	punct
2	note	note	NN	O	0	ROOT
3	:	:	:	O	2	punct
4	33	33	CD	NUMBER	2	dep
5	-RSB-	-rsb-	-RRB-	O	8	punct
6	30	30	CD	NUMBER	7	compound
7	 	 	CD	NUMBER	8	nummod
8	 	 	NN	O	4	nmod
9	 	 	CD	NUMBER	8	compound
10	 	 	CD	NUMBER	8	compound
11	 	 	CD	NUMBER	8	compound
12	The	the	DT	O	14	det
13	Sinwa	sinwa	JJ	MISC	14	amod
14	directors	director	NNS	O	16	nsubj
15	first	first	RB	ORDINAL	16	advmod
16	had	have	VBD	O	4	acl:relcl
17	an	a	DT	O	18	det
18	inkling	inkling	NN	O	16	dobj
19	of	of	IN	O	21	case
20	the	the	DT	O	21	det
21	assignment	assignment	NN	O	18	nmod
22	on	on	IN	O	24	case
23	9	9	CD	NUMBER	24	nummod
24	 	 	CD	NUMBER	21	nmod
25	September	September	NNP	DATE	16	nmod:tmod
26	2008	2008	CD	DATE	25	nummod
27	when	when	WRB	O	29	advmod
28	Kjell	Kjell	NNP	PERSON	29	nsubj
29	informed	inform	VBD	O	16	advcl
30	them	they	PRP	O	29	dobj
31	by	by	IN	O	32	case
32	email	email	NN	O	29	nmod
33	that	that	IN	O	39	mark
34	``	``	``	O	39	punct
35	Nordic	nordic	JJ	MISC	36	amod
36	 	 	NN	O	39	nsubj
37	would	would	MD	O	39	aux
38	be	be	VB	O	39	aux
39	taking	take	VBG	O	29	ccomp
40	over	over	IN	O	43	case
41	the	the	DT	O	43	det
42	seismic	seismic	JJ	O	43	amod
43	operation	operation	NN	O	39	nmod
44	of	of	IN	O	46	case
45	the	the	DT	O	46	det
46	Vessel	vessel	NN	O	43	nmod
47	and	and	CC	O	29	cc
48	would	would	MD	O	51	aux
49	be	be	VB	O	51	aux
50	``	``	``	O	51	punct
51	dealing	deal	VBG	O	29	conj
52	direct	direct	JJ	O	53	amod
53	 	 	NN	O	51	dobj
54	with	with	IN	O	55	case
55	TGS	tgs	NN	ORGANIZATION	51	nmod
56	``	``	``	O	55	punct
57	for	for	IN	O	60	case
58	the	the	DT	O	60	det
59	overall	overall	JJ	O	60	amod
60	operation	operation	NN	O	55	nmod
61	of	of	IN	O	64	case
62	the	the	DT	O	64	det
63	vessel	vessel	NN	O	64	compound
64	 	 	NN	O	60	nmod
65	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	-LSB-	-lsb-	-LRB-	O	2	punct
2	note	note	NN	O	0	ROOT
3	:	:	:	O	2	punct
4	34	34	CD	NUMBER	2	dep
5	-RSB-	-rsb-	-RRB-	O	7	punct
6	Mike	Mike	NNP	PERSON	7	compound
7	Sim	Sim	NNP	PERSON	12	nsubj
8	and	and	CC	O	7	cc
9	Lay	Lay	NNP	PERSON	10	compound
10	Ling	Ling	NNP	PERSON	7	conj
11	both	both	CC	O	12	advmod
12	sought	seek	VBD	O	4	acl:relcl
13	clarification	clarification	NN	O	12	dobj
14	from	from	IN	O	15	case
15	him	he	PRP	O	12	nmod
16	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	In	in	IN	O	2	case
2	reply	reply	NN	O	23	nmod
3	to	to	TO	O	6	case
4	Mike	Mike	NNP	PERSON	6	compound
5	Sim	Sim	NNP	PERSON	6	compound
6	 	 	NNP	O	2	nmod
7	s	be	VBZ	O	8	cop
8	query	query	NN	O	6	acl:relcl
9	on	on	IN	O	14	case
10	whether	whether	IN	O	14	mark
11	``	``	``	O	14	punct
12	Nordic	nordic	JJ	MISC	13	amod
13	 	 	NN	O	14	nsubj
14	referred	refer	VBN	O	8	nmod
15	to	to	TO	O	17	case
16	Nordic	nordic	JJ	O	17	amod
17	International	International	NNP	O	14	nmod
18	or	or	CC	O	14	cc
19	Nordic	nordic	JJ	O	20	amod
20	Maritime	Maritime	NNP	O	14	conj
21	,	,	,	O	23	punct
22	Kjell	Kjell	NNP	PERSON	23	nsubj
23	answered	answer	VBD	O	0	ROOT
24	that	that	IN	O	28	mark
25	it	it	PRP	O	28	nsubj
26	was	be	VBD	O	28	cop
27	the	the	DT	O	28	det
28	latter	latter	JJ	O	23	ccomp
29	,	,	,	O	23	punct
30	but	but	CC	O	23	cc
31	assured	assure	VBN	O	23	conj
32	Mike	Mike	NNP	PERSON	33	compound
33	Sim	Sim	NNP	PERSON	31	dobj
34	that	that	IN	O	41	mark
35	there	there	EX	O	41	expl
36	would	would	MD	O	41	aux
37	be	be	VB	O	41	cop
38	``	``	``	O	41	punct
39	no	no	DT	O	41	neg
40	financial	financial	JJ	O	41	amod
41	implications	implication	NNS	O	31	ccomp
42	 	 	VBP	O	41	acl:relcl
43	for	for	IN	O	45	case
44	Nordic	nordic	JJ	O	45	amod
45	International	International	NNP	O	42	nmod
46	.	.	.	O	23	punct

1	-LSB-	-lsb-	-LRB-	O	2	punct
2	note	note	NN	O	9	nsubj
3	:	:	:	O	2	punct
4	35	35	CD	NUMBER	2	dep
5	-RSB-	-rsb-	-RRB-	O	9	punct
6	Similarly	similarly	RB	O	9	advmod
7	,	,	,	O	9	punct
8	Kjell	Kjell	NNP	PERSON	9	nsubj
9	told	tell	VBD	O	0	ROOT
10	Lay	Lay	NNP	PERSON	11	compound
11	Ling	Ling	NNP	PERSON	9	dobj
12	that	that	IN	O	17	mark
13	there	there	EX	O	17	expl
14	would	would	MD	O	17	aux
15	be	be	VB	O	17	cop
16	no	no	DT	O	17	neg
17	changes	change	NNS	O	9	ccomp
18	to	to	TO	O	21	case
19	the	the	DT	O	21	det
20	Time	Time	NNP	ORGANIZATION	21	compound
21	Charter	Charter	NNP	ORGANIZATION	17	nmod
22	.	.	.	O	9	punct

1	-LSB-	-lsb-	-LRB-	O	2	punct
2	note	note	NN	O	0	ROOT
3	:	:	:	O	2	punct
4	36	36	CD	NUMBER	15	nummod
5	-RSB-	-rsb-	-RRB-	O	15	punct
6	31	31	CD	NUMBER	15	nummod
7	 	 	CD	NUMBER	15	nummod
8	 	 	NN	O	15	compound
9	 	 	CD	NUMBER	15	nummod
10	 	 	CD	NUMBER	15	nummod
11	 	 	CD	NUMBER	15	nummod
12	Morten	Morten	NNP	O	15	compound
13	 	 	CD	NUMBER	15	nummod
14	s	s	NNS	O	15	compound
15	position	position	NN	O	16	nsubj
16	is	be	VBZ	O	2	dep
17	that	that	IN	O	21	mark
18	the	the	DT	O	19	det
19	MOA	MOA	NNP	O	21	nsubj
20	only	only	RB	O	21	advmod
21	constituted	constitute	VBD	O	16	ccomp
22	an	a	DT	O	23	det
23	agreement	agreement	NN	O	21	dobj
24	to	to	TO	O	25	mark
25	assign	assign	VB	O	23	acl
26	,	,	,	O	21	punct
27	and	and	CC	O	21	cc
28	that	that	IN	O	33	mark
29	the	the	DT	O	31	det
30	actual	actual	JJ	O	31	amod
31	assignment	assignment	NN	O	33	nsubjpass
32	was	be	VBD	O	33	auxpass
33	effected	effect	VBN	O	21	conj
34	by	by	IN	O	36	case
35	the	the	DT	O	36	det
36	exchange	exchange	NN	O	33	nmod
37	of	of	IN	O	38	case
38	letters	letter	NNS	O	36	nmod
39	between	between	IN	O	40	case
40	BGP	bgp	NN	O	38	nmod
41	and	and	CC	O	40	cc
42	NGS	ngs	NN	O	40	conj
43	on	on	IN	O	44	case
44	22	22	CD	DATE	33	nmod
45	September	September	NNP	DATE	33	nmod:tmod
46	2008	2008	CD	DATE	45	nummod
47	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	Therefore	therefore	RB	O	4	advmod
2	,	,	,	O	4	punct
3	Morten	Morten	NNP	PERSON	4	nsubj
4	claims	claim	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
5	that	that	IN	O	20	mark
6	Kjell	Kjell	NNP	PERSON	8	compound
7	 	 	CD	NUMBER	8	nummod
8	s	s	NNS	O	9	compound
9	email	email	NN	O	20	nsubj
10	of	of	IN	O	12	case
11	9	9	CD	DATE	12	nummod
12	September	September	NNP	DATE	9	nmod
13	2008	2008	CD	DATE	12	nummod
14	to	to	TO	O	16	case
15	Mike	Mike	NNP	PERSON	16	compound
16	Sim	Sim	NNP	PERSON	12	nmod
17	and	and	CC	O	16	cc
18	Lay	Lay	NNP	O	19	compound
19	Ling	Ling	NNP	PERSON	16	conj
20	constituted	constitute	VBD	O	4	ccomp
21	notice	notice	NN	O	20	dobj
22	of	of	IN	O	24	case
23	the	the	DT	O	24	det
24	assignment	assignment	NN	O	21	nmod
25	before	before	IN	O	28	mark
26	it	it	PRP	O	28	nsubjpass
27	was	be	VBD	O	28	auxpass
28	executed	execute	VBN	O	20	advcl
29	.	.	.	O	4	punct

1	-LSB-	-lsb-	-LRB-	O	2	punct
2	note	note	NN	O	0	ROOT
3	:	:	:	O	2	punct
4	37	37	CD	NUMBER	2	dep
5	-RSB-	-rsb-	-RRB-	O	4	punct
6	This	this	DT	O	7	det
7	submission	submission	NN	O	12	nsubj
8	is	be	VBZ	O	12	cop
9	of	of	IN	O	12	case
10	no	no	DT	O	12	neg
11	legal	legal	JJ	O	12	amod
12	consequence	consequence	NN	O	4	acl:relcl
13	in	in	IN	O	15	case
14	any	any	DT	O	15	det
15	event	event	NN	O	12	nmod
16	since	since	IN	O	29	mark
17	,	,	,	O	29	punct
18	as	as	IN	O	21	mark
19	I	I	PRP	O	21	nsubj
20	have	have	VBP	O	21	aux
21	observed	observe	VBN	O	29	advcl
22	at	at	IN	O	24	case
23	-LSB-	-lsb-	-LRB-	O	24	punct
24	26	26	CD	NUMBER	21	advcl
25	-RSB-	-rsb-	-RRB-	O	24	punct
26	above	above	IN	O	24	case
27	,	,	,	O	29	punct
28	there	there	EX	O	29	expl
29	was	be	VBD	O	12	advcl
30	never	never	RB	O	29	neg
31	any	any	DT	O	33	det
32	valid	valid	JJ	O	33	amod
33	assignment	assignment	NN	O	29	nsubj
34	of	of	IN	O	37	case
35	the	the	DT	O	37	det
36	Time	Time	NNP	ORGANIZATION	37	compound
37	Charter	Charter	NNP	ORGANIZATION	33	nmod
38	to	to	TO	O	39	mark
39	begin	begin	VB	O	33	acl
40	with	with	IN	O	39	nmod
41	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	Therefore	therefore	RB	O	3	advmod
2	strictly	strictly	RB	O	3	advmod
3	speaking	speak	VBG	O	15	csubj
4	,	,	,	O	3	punct
5	whether	whether	IN	O	12	mark
6	the	the	DT	O	10	det
7	requisite	requisite	JJ	O	10	amod
8	``	``	``	O	10	punct
9	notice	notice	NN	O	10	compound
10	 	 	NN	O	12	nsubjpass
11	was	be	VBD	O	12	auxpass
12	given	give	VBN	O	3	ccomp
13	does	do	VBZ	O	15	aux
14	not	not	RB	O	15	neg
15	arise	arise	VB	O	0	ROOT
16	.	.	.	O	15	punct

1	32	32	CD	NUMBER	2	compound
2	 	 	CD	NUMBER	3	nummod
3	 	 	NN	O	20	ccomp
4	 	 	CD	NUMBER	5	compound
5	 	 	CD	NUMBER	3	amod
6	 	 	CD	NUMBER	5	dep
7	Notwithstanding	notwithstanding	IN	O	9	case
8	the	the	DT	O	9	det
9	dispute	dispute	NN	O	6	nmod
10	over	over	IN	O	13	case
11	the	the	DT	O	13	det
12	actual	actual	JJ	O	13	amod
13	date	date	NN	O	9	nmod
14	of	of	IN	O	16	case
15	the	the	DT	O	16	det
16	assignment	assignment	NN	O	13	nmod
17	,	,	,	O	20	punct
18	it	it	PRP	O	20	nsubj
19	is	be	VBZ	O	20	cop
20	undisputed	undisputed	JJ	O	0	ROOT
21	that	that	IN	O	25	mark
22	Morten	Morten	NNP	PERSON	25	nsubj
23	did	do	VBD	O	25	aux
24	not	not	RB	O	25	neg
25	involve	involve	VB	O	20	ccomp
26	the	the	DT	O	28	det
27	Sinwa	Sinwa	NNP	O	28	compound
28	directors	director	NNS	O	25	dobj
29	in	in	IN	O	31	case
30	the	the	DT	O	31	det
31	discussions	discussion	NNS	O	25	nmod
32	with	with	IN	O	33	case
33	BGP	bgp	NN	O	31	nmod
34	over	over	IN	O	37	case
35	the	the	DT	O	37	det
36	purported	purported	JJ	O	37	amod
37	assignment	assignment	NN	O	33	nmod
38	.	.	.	O	20	punct

1	Morten	Morten	NNP	PERSON	3	nsubj
2	ostensibly	ostensibly	RB	O	3	advmod
3	justified	justify	VBD	O	0	ROOT
4	this	this	DT	O	5	det
5	approach	approach	NN	O	3	dobj
6	on	on	IN	O	8	case
7	the	the	DT	O	8	det
8	basis	basis	NN	O	3	nmod
9	that	that	WDT	O	32	dobj
10	so	so	RB	O	11	advmod
11	long	long	RB	O	15	advmod
12	as	as	IN	O	15	mark
13	he	he	PRP	O	15	nsubj
14	had	have	VBD	O	15	aux
15	taken	take	VBN	O	32	advcl
16	steps	step	NNS	O	15	dobj
17	to	to	TO	O	18	mark
18	ensure	ensure	VB	O	15	advcl
19	that	that	IN	O	25	mark
20	Nordic	nordic	JJ	O	21	amod
21	International	International	NNP	O	25	nsubj
22	was	be	VBD	O	25	cop
23	not	not	RB	O	25	neg
24	any	any	DT	O	25	nmod:npmod
25	worse	worse	JJR	O	18	ccomp
26	off	off	RP	O	29	dep
27	from	from	IN	O	29	case
28	the	the	DT	O	29	det
29	assignment	assignment	NN	O	25	advcl
30	,	,	,	O	32	punct
31	there	there	EX	O	32	expl
32	was	be	VBD	O	8	acl:relcl
33	no	no	DT	O	34	neg
34	necessity	necessity	NN	O	32	nsubj
35	to	to	TO	O	36	mark
36	involve	involve	VB	O	34	acl
37	them	they	PRP	O	36	dobj
38	in	in	IN	O	40	case
39	the	the	DT	O	40	det
40	discussions	discussion	NNS	O	36	nmod
41	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	His	he	PRP$	O	2	nmod:poss
2	aim	aim	NN	O	3	nsubj
3	was	be	VBD	O	0	ROOT
4	to	to	TO	O	5	mark
5	maintain	maintain	VB	O	3	xcomp
6	a	a	DT	O	9	det
7	good	good	JJ	O	9	amod
8	commercial	commercial	JJ	O	9	amod
9	relationship	relationship	NN	O	5	dobj
10	with	with	IN	O	11	case
11	BGP	bgp	NN	O	5	nmod
12	given	give	VBN	O	11	acl
13	that	that	IN	O	21	mark
14	the	the	DT	O	17	det
15	seismic	seismic	JJ	O	17	amod
16	services	service	NNS	O	17	compound
17	industry	industry	NN	O	21	nsubj
18	was	be	VBD	O	21	cop
19	a	a	DT	O	21	det
20	niche	niche	NN	O	21	compound
21	market	market	NN	O	12	ccomp
22	with	with	IN	O	25	case
23	very	very	RB	O	24	advmod
24	few	few	JJ	O	25	amod
25	players	player	NNS	O	21	nmod
26	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	-LSB-	-lsb-	-LRB-	O	2	punct
2	note	note	NN	O	0	ROOT
3	:	:	:	O	2	punct
4	38	38	CD	NUMBER	2	dep
5	-RSB-	-rsb-	-RRB-	O	4	punct
6	He	he	PRP	O	9	nsubj
7	did	do	VBD	O	9	aux
8	not	not	RB	O	9	neg
9	think	think	VB	O	4	acl:relcl
10	Nordic	nordic	JJ	O	11	amod
11	International	International	NNP	O	12	nsubj
12	had	have	VBD	O	9	ccomp
13	any	any	DT	O	14	det
14	reason	reason	NN	O	12	dobj
15	to	to	TO	O	16	mark
16	withhold	withhold	VB	O	14	acl
17	approval	approval	NN	O	16	dobj
18	of	of	IN	O	20	case
19	the	the	DT	O	20	det
20	assignment	assignment	NN	O	17	nmod
21	since	since	IN	O	23	mark
22	there	there	EX	O	23	expl
23	was	be	VBD	O	16	advcl
24	to	to	TO	O	27	mark
25	be	be	VB	O	27	cop
26	no	no	DT	O	27	neg
27	change	change	NN	O	23	xcomp
28	in	in	IN	O	30	case
29	the	the	DT	O	30	det
30	terms	term	NNS	O	27	nmod
31	of	of	IN	O	34	case
32	the	the	DT	O	34	det
33	Time	Time	NNP	O	34	compound
34	Charter	Charter	NNP	O	30	nmod
35	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	-LSB-	-lsb-	-LRB-	O	2	punct
2	note	note	NN	O	0	ROOT
3	:	:	:	O	2	punct
4	39	39	CD	NUMBER	8	advmod
5	-RSB-	-rsb-	-RRB-	O	4	punct
6	In	in	IN	O	8	case
7	his	he	PRP$	O	8	nmod:poss
8	mind	mind	NN	O	12	nmod
9	,	,	,	O	12	punct
10	he	he	PRP	O	12	nsubjpass
11	was	be	VBD	O	12	auxpass
12	concerned	concern	VBN	O	2	parataxis
13	that	that	IN	O	23	mark
14	if	if	IN	O	19	mark
15	the	the	DT	O	17	det
16	Sinwa	Sinwa	NNP	LOCATION	17	compound
17	directors	director	NNS	O	19	nsubjpass
18	were	be	VBD	O	19	auxpass
19	consulted	consult	VBN	O	23	advcl
20	,	,	,	O	23	punct
21	it	it	PRP	O	23	nsubj
22	might	might	MD	O	23	aux
23	scuttle	scuttle	VB	O	12	ccomp
24	the	the	DT	O	27	det
25	whole	whole	JJ	O	27	amod
26	assignment	assignment	NN	O	27	compound
27	arrangement	arrangement	NN	O	23	dobj
28	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	-LSB-	-lsb-	-LRB-	O	2	punct
2	note	note	NN	O	0	ROOT
3	:	:	:	O	2	punct
4	40	40	CD	NUMBER	2	dep
5	-RSB-	-rsb-	-RRB-	O	8	punct
6	33	33	CD	NUMBER	7	compound
7	 	 	CD	NUMBER	8	nummod
8	 	 	NN	O	4	nmod
9	 	 	CD	NUMBER	8	compound
10	 	 	CD	NUMBER	8	compound
11	 	 	CD	NUMBER	8	compound
12	Sinwa	Sinwa	NNP	O	13	nsubj
13	wrote	write	VBD	O	4	acl:relcl
14	to	to	TO	O	15	case
15	Morten	Morten	NNP	PERSON	13	nmod
16	on	on	IN	O	17	case
17	23	23	CD	DATE	15	nmod
18	October	October	NNP	DATE	13	nmod:tmod
19	2008	2008	CD	DATE	18	nummod
20	to	to	TO	O	21	mark
21	place	place	VB	O	13	xcomp
22	on	on	IN	O	23	case
23	record	record	NN	O	21	nmod
24	its	its	PRP$	O	25	nmod:poss
25	objections	objection	NNS	O	21	dobj
26	to	to	TO	O	29	case
27	the	the	DT	O	29	det
28	purported	purported	JJ	O	29	amod
29	assignment	assignment	NN	O	25	nmod
30	.	.	.	O	2	punct
