1	C_2017221EN.01002101.xml	c_2017221en.01002101.xml	NN	O	5	compound
2	10.7.2017	10.7.2017	CD	DATE	5	nummod
3	EN	EN	NNP	O	5	compound
4	Official	Official	NNP	O	5	compound
5	Journal	Journal	NNP	O	0	ROOT
6	of	of	IN	O	10	case
7	the	the	DT	O	10	det
8	European	European	NNP	ORGANIZATION	10	compound
9	Union	Union	NNP	ORGANIZATION	10	compound
10	C	C	NNP	O	5	nmod
11	221/21	221/21	CD	NUMBER	12	nummod
12	Judgment	judgment	NN	O	10	dep
13	of	of	IN	O	16	case
14	the	the	DT	O	16	det
15	General	General	NNP	O	16	compound
16	Court	Court	NNP	O	12	nmod
17	of	of	IN	O	18	case
18	18	18	CD	DATE	16	nmod
19	May	May	NNP	DATE	16	nmod:tmod
20	2017	2017	CD	DATE	19	nummod
21	--	--	:	O	12	punct
22	Panzeri	Panzeri	NNP	PERSON	24	compound
23	v	v	LS	O	24	dep
24	Parliament	Parliament	NNP	ORGANIZATION	12	dep
25	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	24	punct
26	Case	Case	NNP	O	27	compound
27	T-166	T-166	NNP	O	24	dep
28	/	/	:	O	29	punct
29	16	16	CD	NUMBER	24	dep
30	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	24	punct
31	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	32	punct
32	1	1	LS	NUMBER	24	dep
33	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	32	punct
34	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	36	punct
35	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	36	punct
36	Rules	rule	NNS	O	10	nmod
37	governing	govern	VBG	O	36	acl
38	the	the	DT	O	39	det
39	payment	payment	NN	O	37	dobj
40	of	of	IN	O	41	case
41	expenses	expense	NNS	O	39	nmod
42	and	and	CC	O	41	cc
43	allowances	allowance	NNS	O	41	conj
44	to	to	TO	O	45	case
45	Members	member	NNS	O	37	nmod
46	of	of	IN	O	49	case
47	the	the	DT	O	49	det
48	European	European	NNP	ORGANIZATION	49	compound
49	Parliament	Parliament	NNP	ORGANIZATION	45	nmod
50	-	-	:	O	45	punct
51	Parliamentary	parliamentary	JJ	O	53	amod
52	assistance	assistance	NN	O	53	compound
53	allowance	allowance	NN	O	45	dep
54	-	-	:	O	53	punct
55	Recovery	recovery	NN	O	53	dep
56	of	of	IN	O	57	case
57	sums	sum	NNS	O	55	nmod
58	unduly	unduly	RB	O	59	advmod
59	paid	pay	VBN	O	57	amod
60	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	53	punct
61	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	36	punct
62	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	63	punct
63	2017/C	2017/c	NN	O	5	appos
64	221/27	221/27	CD	NUMBER	63	nummod
65	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	63	punct
66	Language	language	NN	O	5	dep
67	of	of	IN	O	69	case
68	the	the	DT	O	69	det
69	case	case	NN	O	66	nmod
70	:	:	:	O	5	punct
71	Italian	italian	JJ	MISC	72	amod
72	Parties	party	NNS	O	5	dep
73	Applicant	applicant	NN	O	72	dep
74	:	:	:	O	5	punct
75	Pier	Pier	NNP	PERSON	77	compound
76	Antonio	Antonio	NNP	PERSON	77	compound
77	Panzeri	Panzeri	NNP	PERSON	5	dep
78	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	80	punct
79	Calusco	Calusco	NNP	O	80	compound
80	d'Adda	d'Adda	NNP	O	77	appos
81	,	,	,	O	80	punct
82	Italy	Italy	NNP	LOCATION	80	dep
83	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	80	punct
84	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	85	punct
85	represented	represent	VBN	O	77	dep
86	by	by	IN	O	89	case
87	:	:	:	O	89	punct
88	C.	C.	NNP	PERSON	89	compound
89	Cerami	Cerami	NNP	PERSON	85	advcl
90	,	,	,	O	89	punct
91	lawyer	lawyer	NN	O	89	appos
92	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	85	punct
93	Defendant	defendant	NN	O	77	dep
94	:	:	:	O	93	punct
95	European	European	NNP	ORGANIZATION	96	compound
96	Parliament	Parliament	NNP	ORGANIZATION	93	dep
97	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	98	punct
98	represented	represent	VBN	O	96	dep
99	by	by	IN	O	113	case
100	:	:	:	O	113	punct
101	N.	N.	NNP	PERSON	102	compound
102	Lorenz	Lorenz	NNP	PERSON	113	nsubj
103	,	,	,	O	102	punct
104	A.	A.	NNP	PERSON	105	compound
105	Caiola	Caiola	NNP	PERSON	102	appos
106	,	,	,	O	105	punct
107	G.	G.	NNP	PERSON	108	compound
108	Corstens	Corstens	NNP	PERSON	105	conj
109	and	and	CC	O	105	cc
110	S.	S.	NNP	PERSON	111	compound
111	Seyr	Seyr	NNP	PERSON	105	conj
112	,	,	,	O	102	punct
113	acting	act	VBG	O	98	advcl
114	as	as	IN	O	115	case
115	Agents	agent	NNS	O	113	nmod
116	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	98	punct
117	Re	Re	NNP	O	96	dep
118	:	:	:	O	117	punct
119	Application	application	NN	O	117	dep
120	on	on	IN	O	122	case
121	the	the	DT	O	122	det
122	basis	basis	NN	O	119	nmod
123	of	of	IN	O	126	case
124	Article	Article	NNP	O	126	compound
125	263	263	CD	NUMBER	126	nummod
126	TFEU	tfeu	NN	O	122	nmod
127	seeking	seek	VBG	O	119	acl
128	the	the	DT	O	129	det
129	annulment	annulment	NN	O	127	dobj
130	of	of	IN	O	132	case
131	the	the	DT	O	132	det
132	decision	decision	NN	O	129	nmod
133	of	of	IN	O	136	case
134	the	the	DT	O	136	det
135	General	General	NNP	ORGANIZATION	136	compound
136	Secretariat	Secretariat	NNP	ORGANIZATION	132	nmod
137	of	of	IN	O	139	case
138	the	the	DT	O	139	det
139	Parliament	Parliament	NNP	ORGANIZATION	136	nmod
140	of	of	IN	O	141	case
141	11	11	CD	DATE	139	nmod
142	February	February	NNP	DATE	127	nmod:tmod
143	2016	2016	CD	DATE	142	nummod
144	concerning	concern	VBG	O	127	dep
145	the	the	DT	O	146	det
146	recovery	recovery	NN	O	144	dobj
147	from	from	IN	O	149	case
148	the	the	DT	O	149	det
149	applicant	applicant	NN	O	144	nmod
150	of	of	IN	O	152	case
151	the	the	DT	O	152	det
152	sum	sum	NN	O	149	nmod
153	of	of	IN	O	154	case
154	EUR	eur	$	O	152	nmod
155	83	83	CD	NUMBER	156	compound
156	764,34	764,34	CD	NUMBER	154	nummod
157	and	and	CC	O	149	cc
158	of	of	IN	O	161	case
159	the	the	DT	O	161	det
160	debit	debit	NN	O	161	compound
161	note	note	NN	O	149	conj
162	relating	relate	VBG	O	161	acl
163	thereto	thereto	RB	O	162	advmod
164	of	of	IN	O	167	case
165	the	the	DT	O	167	det
166	same	same	JJ	O	167	amod
167	date	date	NN	O	119	nmod
168	.	.	.	O	5	punct

1	Dismisses	dismiss	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
2	the	the	DT	O	3	det
3	action	action	NN	O	1	dobj
4	;	;	:	O	3	punct
5	2	2	LS	NUMBER	3	dep
6	.	.	.	O	1	punct

1	Orders	order	NNS	O	5	compound
2	Mr	Mr	NNP	O	5	compound
3	Pier	Pier	NNP	PERSON	5	compound
4	Antonio	Antonio	NNP	PERSON	5	compound
5	Panzeri	Panzeri	NNP	PERSON	7	nsubj
6	to	to	TO	O	7	mark
7	pay	pay	VB	O	0	ROOT
8	the	the	DT	O	9	det
9	costs	cost	NNS	O	7	dobj
10	.	.	.	O	7	punct

1	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	2	punct
2	1	1	LS	NUMBER	4	dep
3	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	2	punct
4	OJ	oj	NN	ORGANIZATION	0	ROOT
5	C	c	NN	O	6	dep
6	200	200	CD	NUMBER	4	nmod
7	,	,	,	O	4	punct
8	6.6.2016	6.6.2016	CD	DATE	4	amod
9	.	.	.	O	4	punct

